ï»¿
USU A NTE
[No Limit Entertainment)
ï»¿
•^••^W’ ^>
?. c ^-Z
ï»¿
^
tv, ^-
k? b
ï»¿
OSWBp i^o^^
Q@@»§ramW02 (teEfe@fec6fl£»a
ASSISTANT EDITOR Dacosta Asare
EDITING & MUSIC SCORE
P nm!?)1 ! '"^ ^liro M^tro lAArihLvH/ l
PRODUCTION
Can't you see she is a nice wQman?
mine?
How? What do you mean?
Don't you see it will be ni^e if I have affair with her?
[laughter]
I can make if happen!
Help me to haye her.
If you help me to have her,
you can^t imagine what I will do for you.
Don't worry. Money is not my problem.
I can make it happen!
I don't spend money on any building or ear.
I spend my mopLey on pleasure.
How are you?
<3M fine.
ï»¿
Somebody is very much interested in you
-Is it you?
hie, interested in you for what?
And I am also not interested in you.
Aduana is deepl in love with you.
-T. is?
ï»¿
Don^you know it is his own car? ^-You lie.
Tilly
Don't you need the car key for anythin ?
ï»¿
Don't you see_this is my own car? I carn burn it right now.
Won't you eat any thing?
Won'tjjgu ejf£*arnything? The wGHWn'^fbdjd is ready
If you ar^ rnterested^ I ca’if.bjjy s^me for you.
Is a nice food. I buy some home every day.
So you will go home after close of work?
-Yes
Then you sleep
-Sleep where?
In your house. -Yes, that is where I live.
ï»¿
I just don't know what to say. It's like I am short of words.
I amjiust trying to say^s’omM'hjng.
Then I gues you bath every morning before comin to work.
Why wouldn't I batft You donr't you bath?
Sometimes I don't Uafe.
You will break the chair.
I thought it was my car.
Don't you need the food right now?
I neecl it. Then l5t?s go'.
Gan't you driwe, so I could giXe;you the car.
Unless you take me to driving school.
Go and buy the rice.
Let's go and let me buy it for you.
Why?
There is a gutter at you bask.
What do you mean by that?
It's ok let's go.
My customers will meet my absence so just go-.
Alright take the kay. ^have money in the car. Don't let anyone take it.
ï»¿
Where are you going
I am in need of money so I am going to collect my money.
What d® you sell that you have people owing you?
ï»¿
What do you mean by that question?
-But I need to know.
I work hard but you don't know.
What do you sell?
I gave some pants out on credit so I am going to collect the moneys.
How did you get capital for that business?
These are the things I don't like about you.
This is how you always spoil my day.
ï»¿
Anytime I meet you like this, I don't make money.
•^< wy
ï»¿
What is your problem?
My problem is that you are worrying me.
I have not seen this dress on you before.
When did you buy it or this one too you went to borrow?
Grand mother why? So don't I have any money on my own?
Do you know all the clothes I have?
The other time, you just came to wash one here.
ï»¿
The way you were quick in washing it makes it suspecious.
Why do you talk about my dressing -I have not seen it before.
Do you know all the clothes I have?
I don't like that.
You don't listen to me. Look at your hairstyle.
You can't even turn your neck.
won't live my life like you
I have taken a different pattern.
You have a nice name but you don't like it.
You call your self empress.
It is a modern name. It didn't come in your days.
Be careful with your life.
You are repeating your mother's bad lifestyle.
ï»¿
So humble yourself.
If I get in to any problem, does it concern you?
That is how your mother lived a reckless life.
She brought me up the same way you brought her up to be reckless.
Who did you want to copy?
Y®u brought me up and I took after you.
Children always take after the one that will bring them up.
This is what you tell me todav. If you get your own problem take it.
I> don't like that.
I don't like that.
ï»¿
Why don't you put up a smiling face?
Is ther^ fuel in my car?
It seems I didnrt buy petrol.
ï»¿
We are here because of what happened last night.
We we here beea^use of what happened last night.
We are here to apologize.
I d'onit want you to ahr^y me^
Please just listen.
He is not a drunkard. Why then did he go to drink?
I am going to buy fuel ip my car.
I am going to buy fuel in my car.
No>w wh^is he trying to tell me?
ï»¿
The persojji who gave me tljie drink added sleeping,tablets.
What we are pleading is for you to give him another chance.
I mean he was just numb.
When I take alcohol, I feel weak.
So you give him another chance.
I won't give him another chance.
-I have advised him a lot.
-I few® advised him a lot.
I won't give him another chance.
-I have advised him a lot.
That is why I didn't want t® accept the proposal.
Do»l think I will give you something bad?
You excuse me for a moment.
-Talk to him very well.
You take this for the afternoon.
Oh stop this.
Y®g aw t®® tjr®ublesom’e.
Please I was deceived into believing that
Do you want to hurt me?
S© tonight I will meet you with weed.
Now they say I should take weed So tonight I will meet yOti. with weed.
ï»¿
Tell her you love her.
He says I should say I love you.
So you don't mean it.
I mean it but was not prepared to say it today.
Leave me alone.
lam going s© take this.
Somebody dropped it in my car so just take it.
He says I should come back for the phone.
So you are also coming to take it, right?
He says I should take the phone and give you the car.
ï»¿
What are you doing?
Are you going to use it now?
Are you-going to use it now?
I will use it at-work tomorrow morning.
You can sleep. What about you?
ï»¿
Don't you feel the presence of a woman?
I feel but you have not told me anything that is why.
So can't you fondle my body
Remember this is the second time.
If I leave you will not have me again.
I told m friend to help me but e didn't come.
ï»¿
►•v
The scripture says the Lord will fight for me.
So the Lord will perform for me.
What do you want the Lord to do for you?
What you want me to do.
ï»¿
VO
^ *88
He does spiritual things.
Do you know what the Lord can do?
ï»¿
Put it down. There is time for everything.
wot
ï»¿
Put it down. There is time for everything.
^^^ ^mt x
ï»¿
Are you not a man?
-I am a driver.
X
Are you not a man?
-I am a driver.
ï»¿
So your you have lost your teeth.
-lam sorry.
That is why I said I will not do it.
/You want to poison me with your teeth.
It is accident
You want to poison me with your teeth.
Everybody will hear of this at the station.
Please give my teeth to me.
ï»¿
What do you care for?
Ga.n you fetch me Hennesey?
That is not a problem.
ï»¿
Let me have a shower.
I can't wait.
Alright just because of the sweat. Go ahead
Wait for me.
^^
Should I go for the drink myself?
ï»¿
I will be ealihg the girl to fetch it for you
b
ï»¿
Pardon me.
I want to go for it myself.
I want to go-for it myself.
ï»¿
How many bottles should I take.
Just a bottle for your self alone.
Which flavor should I take?
I am going to fetch the drink.
-Alright.
ï»¿
Why has she gone with her bag
This is emergency dropping.
-you will pay 4 million.
How much is your daily sale to claim 4 million?
Where are you going
Just drive on.
Don't you have air condition in your car?
There is a fault with it.
Is somebody after you?
My mother has been involved in an accident.
Let pie drive faster. Where are you going?
Take me to the hospital.
No drive me home. She is in the house.
My brakes are not working.
Slow down becatise I am ©ut of danger.
^
&
°Q
ï»¿
My brakes are not working.
I have been involved with four accidents with four cars.
This is the only car that is yet to be involved in accident.
Then let rhe alight in front there.
Just look forward and drive.
You fair ladies are spending our money.
If I get you in my bed -
Let me take that turp to avoid the traffic.
Are you taking me back after escaping?
Escaping from what?
I can make you really laugh
It makes people enjoy my car.
You are funny.
I will alight at this place.
ï»¿
I will call you any time I need you.
Now we are friends.
Do you have t^show y&ur teeth to apply tlpe brakes?
You are funny.
Give me your number.
N© I will rather take yours.
No I will rather take yours.
If I don't take your number you won't call me.
I need you as a friend so I will call you.
You don't love me?
What is your name?
ï»¿
When you sail I will tell you on the phone.
Just represent me with any name.
ï»¿
What is your name?
Just call-me comedy.
-The namefits you rightly.
ï»¿
Go and repair your car.
You are a nice lady. My money.
What did you just say?
What did you just say
It is a name of a new car. -You are looking at my back.
You are looking good.
-Thank you.
Where are you going?
I am picking a friend at the airport.
Is he male of female?
Male.
You are always roaming up and down.
ï»¿
...or getting married, he will be very proud of you.
It is true you are ok in this house.
We are rich but you have to start your own life.
It? is true.
To find a husband and plan your own lives together.
Mum I am late.
ï»¿
So can't you see there is a guest with you?
A
You are no more a guest.
You know your place around here. You can go anywhere in this house.
ï»¿
That is not what I mean He need to know me well.
That is not what I mean He need to knowime^velk
My sister here has said a lot about you.
I thought it was the footballer.
Not you this bulky man.
Why do you talk like this?
I am only playing with him.
Anyway this is my si* packs.
Just take me as I am. I am always jovial.
Don't take me ser-ious.
I know that player sailed Pepe is a lazy player.
He is a good defender.
I thought he was a striker.
So you don't knowHnim and you were talking of
My Pepelis geod.
If you have it, it belongs to us all, can't you see?
That is why I am also dressed like this.
Your husband is my husband as well.
ï»¿
Have we shared anything like this before?
We can share anything but not my man.
Have you seen a person being shared before?
Anyway it never happens.
Come and serve me.
So you finished your drink right now?
This is where I g^i^e to make my self proud. z
Pepe, take my picture with your phone.
Pepe, take my picture1 with your phone.
No I w^lbdo it.
Why are^y^ojn'g this?
Is he not a husbarrato all of us?
’I will be doing the selections for you.
This is how it is going to be on that day.
Are y^u^shy/?
ï»¿
Is the fo^chready?
The house help is attending to it.
We need to find something to eat.
I am going to check the food. Serve me^vifh chicken wings.
You are yeny sociable.
You haven't seen/ much of me yet.
Don't you know I have sent you a friend request on facebook?
I will check when I get home.
I have a lot of pictures there.
Just go through my pictures.
ï»¿
You need to see them.
One more thing.
Are you really serious to marry my sister?
She is the reason I am here.
I don't care much about my family
I am not surprised at all that you don't care about your family.
But you need to have a background knowledge .
I am giving you some information. You need to ask her but not now.
There is a uy who has been spoiling er with money.
He is Musah.
He has been giving her guinea fowls and she has fallen for it.
ï»¿
You know rich ladies fall for just anything small.
You mean who?
Who else are we talking about here?
They broke up just about 4 months ago.
So do your background checks.
Be careful so you are not decieved by any rumours.
The food is ready.
Who is Musah?
This guy who has been following you..
I don't know anybody by that name..
You don't know Musah who has been supplying us with meat?
We sorted ourselves out already. We will be fine.
ï»¿
I am going to bring the food here.
Or you would join me as I go?
Who is Musah?
Are you taking her serious?
I don't know of anyone by that name.
ï»¿
I have told you. all about my past and there is nothing to know. -
Empress just told me you broke up just four months ago. '
ï»¿
I just told him Kwame is the last guy I dated.
Pepe listen, I was just playing on your wits..
I said that to test how serious about her.
You know she is the only child of her parents
and w^e don't want any man to disturb her.
I now see that you reaNy love her.
I can recall the change in your face.
Some games are very dangerous.
I;haye to leave this area.
The lights just went out again.
When;you said you were coming, I .: prepared a cocktail.
ï»¿
It was a mixture of honey, ginger and prekese
Don't you know of this Goektail mixture?
Empress I came to you
What is the matter?
The bathroom is filthy so go and scrub
It- is your turn to scrub the bathroom.
You can'Kbe shouting on me like that.
You oan't be shouting 041 me like that.
Shut up and let me talk.
You are just the landlord's girlfriend and you are doing this?
Your grandmother grew up with my own grandmother.
Y®ur grandmother spent all her money OH sweets
She didn't think of buying a land.
She didn't think ®f buying a land.
Settle down with one man.
Did you see my name written on the walls?
But^M knew it is your turn to scrub So wfc® question are you trying to ask
Wait, my grandmother will come and scrub it.
ï»¿
I don't understand why people say how they struggled to build and rent it out.
When we were girls, we used what we have to get what we want.
I will not sleep with such a man for anything.
I willnot sleep with such a man for anything.
If I sant malje money, ou can't deny/ me of my fee ings.
If I cant make money, ou can't deny
Take care of your grand mother.
Bring your light bill.
Even with my ugly face, I made money from men to care for my mother.
If you want to beg for her, open the bag and pay for her.
Get ®ut of here with your shameful acts.
-Get out of here with your pride.
If we had not kept these furniture here, Would you get a place for your friend?
Are you not out of your mind
This lady can really talk.
I wish you could stay here for about two hours.
How do you mean by that?
Have we, mentioned anybody's name?
Has a man hired a single room for you before?
Yes.
Then you are better than your friend so advise her.
I don't understand why some bush girls get some men to..
Where is the light bill?
-I don't have it.
When are we going on the trip to Dubai?
yvhen I get a new guy
These are the reasons I don't discuss my issues in this house.
You have to leave this place.
It doesn't fit you to be here.
Haven't I told you about this before?
So why did you wait till now?
You tiave to leave this place. It's embarrasing.
I have already made art payment for an estate ouse.
ï»¿
I am sorry for coming, here without your prior information.
Why are you like.this?
I am in a terrible situation now.
I have been drilled by just 2 teenage boys in front of your house.
I can see they have torn your clothes.
They escaped with one of my phones.
See, they torn all my clothes.
I am meeting somebod to take some money at the ank
I also have otherap^iritments
Can you help me with something big I can wear?
I can just manage with^ahything.
Just take a look at me.
Let's go I can give you something to wear.
Even if Luisa has a dress here, I can take it along.
ï»¿
How can this happen on this busy street in front of my house?
Empress just came here.
It's been a while since we met.
Why are^yoXHooking like this?
What is happening
There is toothing going on here.
Empress ju^Game to chan e her
What did you just say
Empress says she has been attacked and are you a police officer?
She is your friend and can come here ,at’any time.
ï»¿
We are friends and you shouldn't be surpr-is.gd by this.
Pepe, tell him what is going on. You just find something to tell her.
You are being a coward. The truth is that I have been here for three days.
I tried several times to leave but he kept me here.
You know the last time you left this house.
You are lying.-Is that not your shirt?
When was the las't-.time you left this house?
Is this not your shirt?
-Her dress was torn.
She forced me and I gave in to him.
Don't you know I love you? Have you seen what you have done?
Do you see what you have done? Why are you shaken like a coward?
I love you.
Is it force for me to love you?
I have already broken the relationship so you better stay with me.
Leave that to me. Pack and leave. You have hopes of getting her back?
I don't love,you. Leave out of here.
Get out of here.
iGive me my items else I won't leave.
Do you want me to assult you? -
She has seen us already so let's go and continue.
Get out of here.
->	» -Why are you being so proud?
I say go!
Somebody wish to have me.
* If I push you, what will you do?
Could you be this wicked
<. v B
ii
^t^'>^
^ EA/er%b©dy,cherish whatever they have
> *
I have rm arriv'd three women.
ï»¿
*Th^K®Mer..one Wat left was a result qf^wltery.
T’his latest ©ne. has been very ' industrious.
'^ .... ^'
ï»¿
That is'why I have given her this house.
That is why^I have given, her this house.
ï»¿
gave ^pu this room for free.
And wTiepe Were is the high way, You don't go by a foot path
ï»¿
WIpY^’ll your granddaughter insult my /wife
Why will y®ur granddaughter insult my wife
Wj^y will your granddaughter insult my wife
AneThne as well?
ï»¿
* < <♦
This is just the beginning and you are behaving like this.
ï»¿
I have taken-i^y decision.
I have.Vakten my decision.
u»_-
ï»¿
Either yodr grandd'atighter leaves the ho 115% or
You leave with her
^Yqu l^ave With her
ï»¿
^
Why are .women so eager with marriage?
ï»¿
^Wpmen have cheapen themselves. ^^ How will sprrifeone like-"
Worn eh> hay e^ohe^pen themselves^ ^owwilil, someone like- -
Are you gojng fo^speak against me?
Please I have net mentioned any name , here.
T'hatds.whatJ^have just said.
Eithef'youMgrranddaug leaves the house or
^>0oo, V
You Keaye with her.
, Please I will apologize.
I do the'sweeping and the scrubbing In the house.
A
ï»¿
So if she doesn't do it and I do it, it is t-he same thing.
■■"4^' z.-
Landlord} dsn't pt-ijie yourself too much with inis house.
TiTere-ane no air conditions in it.
ï»¿
^b • ^
. After-all, blnis'is^hot a self contain.
ï»¿
o0'0*
Haye4 giveri you a room?
ï»¿
^^ ^, ^^^^''f
Eiththery^udeal with my grandmother " and . ' /
leave me out pf^or...
leaA^mye ®ut of it or...
Are^ou g;ping to challenge me?
ï»¿
D.o you the number of cases I have sent t® court?
If you aj=e not careful yours will be the next.
ï»¿
Pe6pje^,^y I am a litigant but see what your daughter is doing.
Apologise fqr yourself because I will le^ve this house
Please I am just saying sorry.
Children of these days are like that.
ï»¿
It^ my grandmother who is being difficult/
This r.o.om is M^tfor my designer goods.
I
ï»¿
Ifthat is what he is saying
.1 will Leave the house for you to stay^ here.
ï»¿
It is my grandmother who need a plase like this not me.
I ©a^'t throw her (3(u.it just like that. That is why I am'begging you.
ï»¿
X *	- ■ri’’' ? ^-A ' 1 V '
I ^. /'
.J^# . ^/ I.	’p^ '
For some time now, this is where I will be lodging.
I hope you won't miss the way.
No, I am very m.uch familiar with all this area.
For some time now, this is where I will be lodging.
■I am planning to fix air conditioner there.
Sol want you to guess how much it is going to cost.
This was to be my private home but the contractor
...didn't build it to my satisfaction.
...didn't build it to my satiSfaetion.
I sold it to someone but he hasn't completed payment
So I have come to occupy it.
You have really done well by putting up such a building.
So this is where I should be picking you from?
Anytime I tell you I am in the house, it will be this place.
You said you will be needing security. Where will they stay to watch?
You said you will be needing security. Where will they stay to watSh?
I will arrange of barb wires for the mean time.
But your walls are not complete. How do you fix barb wires?
There is a way of doing it.
So you will be here for 24 hours
Please I will beg you to have patiense with your grandmother®
Please I will beg you to have patience. . with your/grandmother. . "
As they grow, they go through a lot but Learn to leave with her. „
Please my change?
It is just 1 ced
It's supposed to be 2 cedis.
Is this not your house?
Yes I don't have change.
It's supposed to be 2 cedis.
No it's 1 cedi. The fare is 9 cedis.
I will take it back.
I have no change else I would give you
Or I should give it to you as a gift? -Whatever
You can keep it.
-Alright, bye.
ï»¿
I didn't buy water. How do I live here?
^
ï»¿
This is a real woman with a soft body
If I lay hands on this lady..
If I could win her with money
Then I wouldn't mind going for a bank loan.
At least after spending all the money on her
I will just go to jail.
ï»¿
^JJ
So if a man Joves a woman he always have to say it.
Can't the women see from his facial looks?
ï»¿
Now she has left me with sleepless nights .
So what do I do?
I ean't propose.
If you send someone to propose for you They end up sleeping with the girls.
If I don't get this girl, I will die.
f^en if I have to pay money I will pay.
The other day when I saw her tighs when she was boardig the car..
■Look at all these.
Sueh things like these are always kept irn this kind of container.
See how elastic it looks.
Look at this place. Very tiny.
Oh ladies!
. W-
ï»¿
Everything about beautiful ladies are nice.
The other girl who came here wore something like a pillow case.
V£by dom^t I wear them to bed.
I am not a fool. It is love.
Tih'e love for a woman can make you do crazy things.
S b
What fascinates me most is how women wear pants .
iJust this thing when a man s,ees it he Gets so hard.
Who on this earth has not removed a ladies pant before?
Not even the president.
ï»¿
Why are you not giving me the chance to explain what happened to you?
I know this is your house and I will leave if you don't need me.
But y©u give me a chance to explain myself.
You have done it already so what else? I have not done anything.
The harm has already been caused. There was no harm in what you saw.
She came to me for a new dress because her own got torn.
For your sake I couldn't throw her out.
There was nothing bad in what you came to see.
So you came all the way from your house t«® tell me this story?
I am not here t® convince you but try t® understand me.
She is your friend and I met her through you.
ï»¿
How are you
-I am fine
I am happy I met you.
I board your car because I respect you
I know and I picked you because of your beauty.
What is your name? -Empress, the blessed.
It is even in the bible.
When Joshua was going to the new land his concubine was Empress.
Because the girl was blessed, she got to the land first and prepared it.
I will be meeting a business partner in a hotel and I am not gBing to leave you.
I have an appointment with my pastor
I am a treasurer at church and I have to give him the church money.
I don't go to hotels. The bi&le even speaks against it.
When somebody see me around a hotel and tell my pastor, I will be in trouble.
Let me correct you. What you read is in Psalm 1.
The hotels are not for bad things. It is for business men.
I can't transact my gold business in a private home for security reasons.
You tan't go to heaven ^ith your gold so don't talk about it with much pride.
I supply gold to Nyame Akwan in Obuasi.
I also walk yyith gr^eat men of God. Among them is Ben York.
I have heard much about him. My prophet is Prophet 1.
I am very much particular about your gold business.
Do you have lincense?
Sure. As a business man I have it.
Do you buy them your self or you just keep them for others?
I buy them for the exporters. So you send it through the exporters.
I always walk with mone so your lift
I wouldn't go with you to t-he hotel but from the way we are knowing ...
each other, I am begining to like you
To convert somebody to Christ is persuation. I wish you could join me..
...at church next week. So I will go with you to the hotel.
But I want you to promise me that you have canceled your bad intentions
Don't be taken over by any bad intentions as the devil tempted Jesus.
There would be no tests. I want God to use me to'Change your life.
I want you to experience new and good things in your life.
Please it hasn't gotten t® that. Let's be fri'ends first.
I will show yotu where I live but for now I want to know yours.
Let's g® t® my hotel.