ï»¿
What are you doing up there?
Things are falling apart.
MW./?
His-sic-kness is getting worse,and there's no money.
So what are you doing up there?
I wanted to go and sell this,and send him to his hometown with the proceeds and take care of him there.
ï»¿
; ^
* ^V>=
You want to sell those utensils and take him to his village to take care if him?
Have you told pastor about this?
I'm just coming from his house.
His wife told me he is not around so what can i do7
His wife told you he is notaround?
Yes.What else can i do?
What is that woman talking about?
I spoke with him this morning and hejs.at home.
So she was lying to me?
I don't even know what is wrong with that woman.
See how powerful pastor is,instead of the woman to be supportive,she is rather pulling him down.
How can a pastor's wife lie like that?
Uncle it's the pastor's wife you are talking about.
Let me say it because she has done enough.
You are in trouble and you need the pastor.
If he dies,it's because she lied to you.
Just calm down.
Don't go and sell anything. I will go and call the pastor myself.
For him to come and pray for him.
I don't know what to do.
Hurry up then.
Meaning you won't go back.
Have a little rest.
I will go there myself.
I can't sleep.
Don't think too much.
ï»¿
Please help me God.
<< X* r '«. •‘A* j. .
Knock in.
Who is it?
Itis me.
I'm looking for pas o .
He is n -aroundi
Please wher^wid 'fre^o??,;^
I said he is not aroufitL What^on'cerns.you with w'h’e‘r£' e'Wfirit?
What is it? We are in ,e that's why we came here,we need the pastor.
So we have to see him/
So we ha^eii^e^hirii;: 4'srm^
You are in needjsjhe*the4iead of your zfahjiiy.^
Young lady,didn't i tell you he is not around?
Yes o i .
So what are you doing here?
My uncle said we should-come and c-hec-k if he is back'S x
I said he is.not around.
Meaning what my niece told bo t ou saying pastor is not around is true.
But he is not around.
■^ ' i^/But he is not around,
I spoVe with pastor this morning and he told me he is at home;
So why do you have to lie to her that he; is not around?
So why do you have to lie_to her that he b Mi arwrj'J?
What you are doing is not good.
You will make me call you a witch with what you are doing.
yer-y^'bdyknbw you in this town as pastor's wife;butiwhat''you are doing is very bad;
You arecalling me a witch7
Yesy/ou are a v.itGh.
Let go of him.
ea e me alone,didn't you hear .'.hat he said?
V/hat do you tend to gain with what you are doing7
lim gaining wirat you are seeing.
i,ou came because
ï»¿
^‘n alrsidy ded-y'S'l sevyj da/s niiilng and prayers ry him.
Which will begin tomorrow,so a I of you should be,part of it.
C^lnj down with nh^ rt: aaz h ggliy ml
V/e are really working on 1.
I know by the time we finish this fasting ano prayers,God wi'l perform a miracle.
PliiiEJjj foryhe me hr eJi mec he happened.
Wi -jko ypolughzi for i/ir/wlng.
/on //111 hear from us 9
Sod dess you.
Don step ■ in this house again.
This is a mission house.
And so wh
So everyone can c-ome ere.
It's for the church.
You are making so much noise abo • r • and Christianity.
You are allAvelc-omelo this meeting. ^
.There are some st s going on i want to mak-! knwjirh /oil
There are some stuffs oing on i want o Taka know • •'
It's all about the pastor and his wife.
1 weft to the r ouse myself.
To advice the wo a at her behaviour bringing shame to the church.
You should've seen vhat happene-.
He insulted me and ent me out of the
I don't reallyore about her \ cisrespec-ting me because i'm her husb’and's assistant.
I don't really care .about her disrespecting me ^cause i'm her husband's assistant.
Even if she doesn't respect me,she should respect her husband at least.
We are lucky this isi ° l^si)igotten to the headquarters,because-if -itxdoes..
.. astor will be in(tr;oub e.
So i called you to tell you that thisjs ;hat is going on.
So as memebers of t e wo en's fellowship,! want yo to advice her.
ife,w are pleading with you that o b io r s bringing hame to the church.
f t b members have even left the chur X
Most of the women have stop women fellowship because of yo
f o go out for evangelism,nobody wants o iste because f your beha iour as a pastor's wife.
I will plead with you :nar g^^®© pastor has wronged you in,-an
..tell us,for s to settle it.
Or if it's the members,we can call them a d settle he issue.
Because this a iour of yours is affecting hie church.
B Gause this behaviour of yours is ffecting the - urch. 1
Pastor's wife.
Talk,because you are making^npise.
Like my sister sa d, eople are talking about rb lour out there.
So please change your'wJysXiecause it's really affecting t e churchy
If the pastor is at a It,you can come o us for us to call him and talk to hi .
If you are the head of a department in sfjursri,!^ -j huga ^ ^
If you are the head of a department-in church,it's a huge task.
Are you done?
If i knew you called me here because of this nonse se,i wpuldn't have come.
Which people are spreading rumours about me?
I don't need you.
I don't even need your head pastorjet alone you.
I just wanted ou to witness this.
I belie e ther s ore to this.
There's more to it because she wasn't like
this.
What will • i , o pray.
I believe whate e -ha is hidden will be
r^ aaler
I believe whatever that is hidden will be revealed.
^^
ï»¿
' ,;M J^'' V5’
ow are you7
Km ok.
What is it tbat'you really want7
(>i
Wh-dtls k?
Why won't yop allow her to^get marrie ?
Why won't yju allo her.to’get married? ■ ^^ *^	•—
*
I'm looking fo a horse to slaughter.
You have to be very careful.
ï»¿
Cl
^Vl '^1^
God being so good she has found someone who wants to marry her but he is sick.
h? don't you want her to go and take are f im?
I'm talking to you.
What is it?
D you really hear yourself?
‘If you were wiseenoug ,you wouldn't come .ere an say this.
is it me you are talking to like this7
Who are you?
I'm somebody.
You are somebody like w o?
What is it? What's the noise all about?
Come and listen to the nonsense he is telling me.
You wouldn't tell me what you are telling me if you were wise.
If she was daughter,would ypu ask her to go and live with a man7
Is she not old enough?
/w aiiilwii^ uJ^ irjou^i
You are not part of this family.
Aren't you my father's child?
My went to flirtaround' nd'gave birth to you if you don’t know.
Your mother was not married,you are a bastard.
^0 q o q o©t p#;of ©s0
^oTi aYe lucky my father left huua^tji-j^ wiy you h-jva -i pfeca tu'Jiya,
Is that what you are telling me?
If i were really your sister you won't tell my daughter to go into that.
IS shi a child?
ï»¿
How old is she9
- -4	" ’
Get out of this ho se.
Calm down.
Dwj'i owns hye yjd alk rn/ fynll/ ksuy;
1 wmj'j li-jvi till pu yl/i rna -j ytw'J •iniwar.
You wantan-answeryforimy daughter, o-gp and live with that-sickien
ï»¿
iet out.
■' ^‘ ‘-^ ‘
t ^ .V
• p
a
Wha^dcTyouxreally want7
ï»¿
■/ Ifyou were not my father's child,i ..'.’jfeld've.'slapped^U! ~
My father left you with that big house^so.. ._
ï»¿
So you are envious of the house myjather ...
gave-me
ï»¿
Stgp'talkjngxand go.
$ '^
J
*
Ypu want.to'destroy my daughter
ï»¿
I '.would've sent her away if she'-was not my. . ' daughter.
It's enough,just go.
Where are you going7
It's ok.
What bible verse did the pastor quote from7
How can an angry person read a bible?
All he said was,we shouldn’t get angry for
You need to have patience and investigate any issue that comes.
What waslhe meaning of what you just did?
Stop what you are saying,i thought you were eve'" coming to tell me something nice.
So.ilm-talking-nonsense?
mummy's behaviour?
I intentionally sent you to bring your other uncle.
For us to talk to your mum,and you just start the meeting without me.
Is that what you are saying? You are a fool.
Instead of you to talk sense into her,you sent her to call her uncle.
ï»¿
Because of that i'm.a fool?
I want a bigger one.
How are you?
> o< 0
I'm fine'"" . ► . a , 0Q(3
/	Where are-ypu:$p'^
My mum senFnlg'.
"SH$'is'.ti"n'£
^■(iw '
«L
I
Sen j h’er my-r.e'^ar.cfs'.
We tnank God,you've agreed for Cin o marjyGeorge.
pJ/ 'J'j'jyiltar £flndy?
te ^ase.
'ilh/ do /on -i^
Sometimes i see bro Chief in that house.
Real y.he goes there7
He goes to pray for him with some asters.
go there more sten?
I’ve seen him three times t ere.
I agreed to it because Gea: GOjriigofJi s getting /.ors
Send your mu"' ^f^ga^fe.
Please don't tell im i sai anything.
17/wj'r ^/ ijfjyiijJrjg.
•wn brother .betrays me.
n.ia^s-i:^.-
Is it wrong i Galled you?'
Why^are you'Galling meZWhafdo ypu .vant?
Am i our sister?
A'm your relative9
Stop what you are doing7
ow can you tell me that just because called you?Aren't you my sister?
If i were your sister,you would'fa us daughter into.a'ditch.
So you are ending.the good-ueiabonship v.e have becaT^eTU 4his?
You d n't want the b^ - e.
W.e.are from the same er
16.
If we are formith'elsame.Viar,e_nfs.affcl vou are a fool/i‘needito,jpakeyo.U'Wise.
You know very well tha • we wanLth'e man abroad to come'and marry Gindv.
And if we are fightingYfdri her not'to liv
with that guy,not knowing you also'gb’^ere behind my ac- .
I want/he bpstjor .erps:®©^
I don't blamte you,because.y;o ’ ? Y gotten a girl pregnan Sat ocr o
You don't have a chHd'S'd ypurhave no compassion.
Has it goften to that-?
I'm telling you thetruth,y'(Ju Ji3ve.no compassion.
If you had a child who'w s tnisb hay.igg like this,you would iTa^ic-onipa s'o r e-
Is she.npt-my’niece?
ï»¿
Ep^Hiyda-g z<’.-n.c her to
r;;e v;ash'ed my hands off henycu eai take
its .oj’wfio is.desperate ora -hik
I've take’
tes
Why -jra you chi-; 'Jlrrkuk?
fsirjgirjg A WWSW SDrJSj
ï»¿
We_are;b'e i in the,seven days fasting and r "ers today.
We are pr' in tio God for divine stren th ,d_p oection.
or our r thert :get‘-'his healing.
In fesus/r 'me,let's pray.
ï»¿
The evil spirit fighting againstthe young, man,is also dwelling in my. wife.
You all .saw how she was be aving recently.
f she has been touche *o, the^rstday
of fastfrtgti believe tge young mams going to get better.
A-.wh cast away any spirit id er.
(PASTOR P..A ING$
^efp h?Hatnd;jp;
Thank God,she is saved.
■ncN believe God will do the rest.
As we have started well,God will lead us to a good finish.
Let's all pray or oyr^r tlierS.
ï»¿
*p
*li
Is this not Mr Menash's phone.
He is my in law.
He is marrje'd to my daughter.
Young lady take your time and talk to me.
What is it?
Take your time and talk,are we fighting?
You are talking on someone's phone,you don't-know me,so don't shout n me.
Mr Mensah is married?
I'm listening.
ï»¿
Let-me alk to im if he is around you.
Young ladyj'm not a c-hild ok.
I might even be your mother's age,so take your time and talk.to me.
live heard you,it's enough.
Ifc’enough,you're still talking.
hat is it?
It's ok,i've heard you.
I've heard you. Thank y.u.
It's ok.
So Mr. Mensah has a wife?
Is that how men are?
So he wanted to marry my daughter and keep e here, >hilehe will be with his wife abroad.
How will i explain this?
They love themselves but i was disagreeing with them;
I was pushing my daughter'into a ditch.
(SINGING A WORSHIP SONG)
Today is Jie ast day of the se en days astJng and prayers.
We are committing our brother unto thy care efore we move there.
May the healing of the Lord visit him even . before^ve getwre?1 q
May the dealing o the Lord visit him even before:we get there.
ï»¿
PASTOR PRA ING)
MfJG ArrWSUTES TO CHIEF PWEa 51$)
ï»¿
Ve are going to pray for him.
We arg^going to-;praVor nim.
for Swl1^ M-jl Md.
ï»¿
-. '•»..*•>■•-
• >
• *
<x
4* ^
ï»¿
-^l?^^
Mining to w.
Stand by me and let Te win.
.Ipyou help me wi
promise to sacrifice a big s
for
; *2S.
Get up /arno
.GetAJ [Twarriors^
I
ï»¿
How are you7
I'm fine. You ^e ?3i^ e.
We are coming to pray to ■ od forihis divine healiRg o im.
Today is the last day of the fasting and prayers we did.
We will pray for a new strength to enter into him.
Let's pray.
(PASTOR PRAYING)
wi^:^ CriA'jrrij'jgj
i
What i your name.
What do you need my name fd ?
What is your nanTe?
My name is Prah.
ou have a name of the ods.
You have to worship the pds.
I won't do that.
Yob have to be in a shnne,you are here making noise.
You were named after a god you need to worship.
Who told ' ou?
I'm suffering and you . there filing me.
I feel very hot.
" Show them what
I'm dying here,stop making, noise.
ï»¿
Get up in Jesus name.
It's God w o deserves all the th n's nd praba.
ere t
God
o 'e it.
God jha aved im;
Ishe healed7
'I'm healed.
The most important thing is to come to church regularly.
The bible says if an evil spirit leaves ne bGdy..it doesn't go far away.
You are repeating'this again.
Yes i'm r eating it.
It hi e ,so when t omes back and the body is wea ,it enters again.
You have to worship God with seriousness.
From now-goi g,do' everything possible to arry her.
Yo havp to understand that in this ife,n • ody forgives easily.
There are evil people arp nd,so everybody needs to walk in the path-qf righteousness.
It is God <0/1 a e you prosper in
Pastor even if he r pgs one bottle of drink i will accept it.
T e e are n’o drinks in this,they are -etting married in the church.
I ylll su/w: by ;;^u;; shaOs my bl;
*4
v
ï»¿
Wait-for me.
V
<9 - ^ v'. ^
I will call her.
What is it?
I'm pleading on their behalf,forgive them.
Even God accepted me back whe He healed me and i never went to church again.
Who are we not to accept them.
We also have to forgive'Iherp.
Forgive them for all they did.
Get up.
(M an g^i /nurrted.
•Thank youm m.
Th^ 15 nt> /' ad dnjjyl/iy inis 1
I Gan^t marry my^wnidaught-er.
What i'v,e seen and heard cannot be explained.
A'llVc-an say is tliat,you.shw'd’qet married.
Well said.
r
Thank you for agreeing to it.