@£^If® ^fe.!sl j^^feii
Comfort, how are you?
You will do nothing if I am not okay, so I am working hard to take care of myself.
That one is possible.
Lopk^atfall these dirt-around, where are the kids7
Is too early oo, is too early!!!
Hmmmm
Doctor Monfncd just called me right now,the doctor wh*d Wok karc'Of :m'e wh'en i was ss’ck
Ik II
-for what?7
He c-alled to ask if i had] eaten, ■and*i said 'no
he asked why, and i replied i dont have money on me
and'He said rcould die beacuse, sake of my situation i d3nt have to starve myself
And i said i have no money on me
He asked of you, and i said you are outside selling
ist 4
Oh then go-to her for some money for. food
And then I remembered,
/4csi ।
tGiye me money for food..-'.
Then death awaits you, you will die for me^get money from loved ones.
vvhy? ii
Any job that i try to do, you collect the.money and missuse it
Any business I try to lay my hands on, you collect the money,,an‘d missuse it
Any business I try to lay my hands on, you collect the money and missuse it
As for this one my'eyes are widely open like a serpent
As for this one my eyes are widely open like a serpent
Last time you took^money I was suppose to spend with thse kids.
You could have use it for food, but you used'it to buy cigaritte
Go to the cigaritte seller, tell her you need your money
Comfort, so should I die out of hunger?
A woman I have kids with and have taken care of you before
And if now I am poor and you have money, should I( die out of hunger and go to hell with nry^iGknessP
Is that so Comfort7
You wont even get a dime 111
Not evenja peny!!, I doht havei1.1’!? •
Not even a peny!!, I dont have !!!!!
so there is no money on you as you*sit there7
do nt have a dime
So you haven't make any sales today7
I said go to the cigaritte seller,! won't even give it to you if there have been sales.
Let me inspect your cloths if there is no money
You have been misusing my sales air this while, when will I get a capital?'
FIGHTING •"
$
Father
Gospi
A
■' 44
Good morning oo
Good morning oo, Gospi
Hope all is well?
By the grace of GOD, this is how He has brought me
Oh its okay, the Lord is alive everything will be just fine
This is my end
why?
I'm messed up,
I'm finished
What is the matter
The end of a man is indeed a sad one !!
What at all is the matter7
Sound of a cutlass
Gospi look at where I'm staying as a care taker
This place...
What has it done?
You withness the time i came, it was like a thick forest
We all know 11
Look al how i have struggled with different kinds of snakes in this house
I tried all my best and killed all these snakes for it to be a better place to stay
All these pythons, Gospi you know what I'm talking about
You shouldn't be surprise if you are walking with animals of all this kind
The income of staying in someones house as a care taker is; fighting with reptiles.
We come to stay in animals kingdom, why are you so surprised
As for last time I almos” slc:'t .. ‘h a sgaike in my room, if it hadn't been the drig iw againsr snakes
are you sure you have snakes drug?
Oh yes i had a little if it, when i went to the North.
That's how i have tried to make this house a better place, it hasn't even been that better
You have done well, it's a house now.
Ofcourse...
My landlord always comes from the city and congratulate me for keeping here clean
Last time he came and i wanted to welcome him but he refused me.
and i said oh why landlord, I respect you a lot
and He told me the house is almost completed, so He is coming to complete it
Trouble has come 1 *
so that my grandchildren will come and stay in, so pack from the house
The landlord told you to leave?
I should leave
And i said oh my landlord
PROVERB....
He said what is the meaning?
And I said, Eeii an elder who doesn"t understand proverbs
I was the one that made this house a better one
and is not an abomination for a helper to enjoy his handy work
To cut long story short, He is giving me three days to leave
And i said oh please i beg you,
The law gives three months to sack someone from your house.
Do you even know what you are saying7
Why
have you rented a house to be given three months to move out?
No I took- care of it.
NO NO, let me tell you...
The misunderstanding between care takers and landlords is move'out, I'm moving in
eave I'm coming to complete my house
Unexpectedly, they will sack you out, and you become stranded like frog
Then He has played me too
And then i said oh landlord
And I begged him to give me the corner of the house to sleep, but he said no
and oneday is even off from the three days he gave me to move out
So Gospi I beg you, as for you i know you
If you can help me lodge at your place for free"
So I could move in with my things
should give you a place for free?
ï»¿
NO
We all human beings
Oh yes we all humans
People are there for people
ï»¿
But people cant let people do good.
so please i can't give it to you for free I need moneys need cash
Ah Gospi I don't understand, explain further please.
I said i will collect money from you I!
Eeii
Why eeii ?
Me i can't carry my things already
Then you will be late
Gospi UM
Nothing is for free in this world,there are no good doings anymore
Show some concern for me
I saw you when you were coming
You saw me coming 77
yes, yes
You saw me like how H?
we all were looking for a place to stay, and you gotup there and I got down here
man please, the owner of the house has given the house to me sake of his bigger mansions in the city
So me Akua Gospi I am a landlord
Oh really I!
h'jy^ jrjjjXEitl ^r * Jjrjly iyjbjftiuajjsy ♦iRhtT
so cancel my name from that list as a care taker, do you hear me7
ï»¿
Eeii why ?'
Mum, they have sack me again
They have sacked you from school again?
Yes
Have been pleading with the principal to consider me write the exams but she saids no, the arrears is too much
Hmm God, marrying an irresponsible man is indeed a sad one
Hey’!!, what even pushed me to marry this man in the beginning
He has really ruined my life
Ern H
look, put your bag down first okay
Mom, haven't you make any sales for today that i can use for the payment
I am not being stingy.
Since morning nobody have even come here
Then i have to stop the school and join you in the charcoal buisness
khaye to stop
Is there not any food7
You put your bag down first and come
Eem this is serious
There is not even food for us to eat in this house
Ern ?
Twum Barimah has really ruined my life
Twum Barimah
Twum’ Barimah!1!
Ohhh talk, we listen with our ears not eyes, ah
When one looks-at you attentively when you are talking,
That is when you notice the person is listening
Is my eyes my ears ?
OH fl
Twum Ba ri ma h
Talk ii
I said find a jobz be responsible in life
tefa1
Why
Why have you let all the responsibilities upon me
Look at our son
Look at how i suffered and struggled for him to complete school
Our daughter is also about to complete
She will also complete and join soon
Then you turn three giants in this house
I'm I lying ?
Why ?
Why have you turn all the responsibilities in this world upon me to struggle
Twum Barimah why ?
Since we started live
You have been moving from one place to the other like a butterfly
We always on the run, till we have landed ourselves in this uncompleted house
Why ?
Een Comfort
What is it 7
Comfort An'oma ?
Oh you are saying stuffs
Have you thought about what you are saying7
Thay said it, that women are ungrateful
Some women are ungrateful, and you are no exception
Me ?
Have you remembered the time
I saw you till now, have you 7
Lumber said it, that women are opportunist
Women are opportunist to the extent that they don’t want to pass through.a day of labor
The time I was with you in the beginning,
And I was struggling here and there 24/7 as you were enjoying
You did nt say anything
And if today doctors says I shouldnt do any hard labor
I shouldn't even build a house, and if I do so I will die
ï»¿
That’s why I am sick and can't even work
And if this short while you are feeding me
you are making noise about it
When have you take a lead in searching of a house7
This one !1
If I hadnt lead this one would we have got it ?
This is the 31st building...
this is the 31st building we have begged for
This is the last one that we have stayed in for long
You are not ashamed of it !!!
I lead all of that
You are ungrateful
Me ungrateful
I'm telling you
You are ungrateful woman H
Me ungrateful ?
didn't believe them
Twum •!
As you are speaking english over here
Find an office and work there as a gate man
Me gate man7
So that we will get something monthly
Gate man as if i'm just a mere person
As you sitting there, what do you expect 7
A royal and a grown man like me as a gate man?
As you sitting there, if not a gate man then what do you expect7
AHH H
Good for nothing, Mr, good for nothing you are always idle why 111
Everyday and everywhere women always talks and makes noise
To put pressure on people
How come 11
How come !11!
Excuse me, I'm afraid
Look at him
How can you tell me that
Foolishness 111
Twum Barimah be responsible, I'm telling you H!!
Erm Twum Barimah
As the saying goes, man rises, when he is in deep waters
) I come in peace, but is not all that peaceful
My landlord is moving me out
And is not easy at all 111
Is it now the time ??
Yes if
Eeii, then this woman has been merciful
She'said her daughter has even called ' her, I dont even know
She could have even informed me
She'just came and said I should leave
So I beg of you
As for your own it's already yours
Juju has helped you snatched the house from the owner
Sb if you can please help me stay here
without paying a peny, so I could start a search party of a room
That's why I came...
Oh okay, Ermm Ofori
Let me tell you something
This world we are in
You won't be successful if you don't choose to be wise
If you don't bully you can never be successful
Eeii ’
And if you dont use your brains you can never be successful
Because
Someone’s money is in the pocket of another's
Someone's money is in the pocket of another's
How can you collect your
You have to be wise and use your brains
There is always direction if you don't know
Do you^understand 7
No huge matter comes with a notice
I alone knows what people have been doing in this world
We the ones that can't build houses with our own money,
but stays in people's houses
vThey bully us alot
So is about time we are also using JUJU to snatch all their houses
And that will be all for you
Eeii ’
You have reported to me how your landlord is moving you out
You have been worrying me all this while
And I have been giving you directions for your place to be permanent for you
You said no
And you are here crying that
(SLAP)
what do want from me Koo Fori
You want to come and stay in my house and then.......
Look, you won't even get my bath room to sleep, not even my kictchen
I won't let you...
Because I'm wiser and older than you are
I know alot than you do know
This is the road to success and you saying no
How can you be successful ?
Oh but Twum it hasn't gotten to slapping
If you dont take care I will slap you
I havent slaped you yet, but if you dont be careful i will slap you
Hmmm U
Ofcourse Twum you said it, that I should use JUJU on my lanlord to take the house permanently
But before God and man...
Everybody knows I'm a catholic
I have been Baptized and goes for communion, i want to go to heaven
So as for that I cant do it
Good
As for me I'm a fool
can't do that
I'm a fool that is why I have occupy a full house all by myself
Een no you are not a fool
Jesus didnt see when you were been sacked away?
Ernn Jesus
Why couldn't he send one of his angels to come rent apartment for you7
That’s what surprises me
Then know that Jesus is bad
Romans killed Jesus
Pilato is a Roman
Herode is a Roman
Amerado is also a Roman
They ve say it
Why did they crucified Jesus
So if you have really taken Jesus, then continue his work
We don't crucify in Ghana but you will suffer as you are in now
So Ofori there is nothing wrong
But i will even charge you to pay 100 cedis to even sleep beneath of my bed every month
Eeiiii !!!
ï»¿
Oh Ghana is so fantastic
Laughing...
Everything is going on well
laughing....
Oh uncle? I will send the money to him
Oh it wasn't enough7 then I will add more
Micheal Jackson
MICHEAL JACKSO'N H!
Hold on we will talk later
Are you deaf 7
Akua what is it ?
I have been shouting your name all this while,or you have forgotten your name?
Give me my money
Which money again?
So you dont pay utility bills and water bills do you want me to pay for you?
Ahh ?
But you collected both together
Can you imagine 7
Can you imagine ?
You even made me pay rent for your bathroom
But if I compare to a hotel here is cool
Why do you want to mke me feel bad
If you stand in court and tells the judge
that when I was collecting money for the rent, i also made you pay utilities
He will say you dont think
He will say you are mad ’’
How can you pay for a utility you haven't even used?
Or you didn't hear me when I said it?
AHH !!
How can you say I have collected you money for bathroom
Have you scrub the bathroom in this house before
I always scrub the bathroom all the time
And is all this same money, I use to buy detergent
How can you tell someone from the states to come and scrub bathroom
If it well to be you who came,
will you do the scrubbing ?
Did you bring any maid when you were coming from states
AHHH !>
Do not worry me beacuse I am really high okay
The house I am building is even bigger than this
then go and stay in
Me I even laid foundation for story building
look if you go to your area then you tell them this bullshit
then you tell them this lies, for me it's childish
It's childish for me okay I!
why didn't you even go to the hotel
What do you think they do at Golden Tulip
Haven't you heard of people popping at Golden Tulip and GolJJmbean
if not haven’t you heard of plus 2?
Haven't you heard of Adonko
Don't worry me young man
I'm giving you uptill tomorrow if not, it won't turn out to be good
you will regret staying in this house
You lucky my gun is not here
Look
the bullet is been swallowed already
Ahh so you deceiving us
You wearing military wear
Camo or whatever, top and down
With gun on top
so you have the licensed to kill
if you kill you go to jail, you will be jailed
long story shorty early in the morning i will be collecting my money
I'm going to pay
You are done, I thought you could get some of the goods I'm bringing home
because almost the things i'm bringing are all your sizes
Hey, hey H! I'm tired of you, you not the one that clothings me young man
You look so beautiful when you speaking come on
come again
Yeah!1
Ofcourse
awwwww you never told me
Laughing M!
look at how soon you camming
Laughing...
I'm not a dog to come this early
come on get up from me H!
I have got you
can you embarrass this way?
You don't calm your self, you want worry me with money issues
so you dont respect your self like that ?
What do you mean ?
You not current, clear off
Clear off ! •
Are you playing with my feelings or me
You not current,
you are very acake, you know nothing
All you know is to apply pomade on your skin
You dont know whatssap, you are a fiasco
Oh young man be fast okay
Owura !!!
bring it and lets go
Or he is consuming the cement 7
Laughing...
so where have you got to ?
Fatner I'm now flowing the top
Eii then you have really done well
Small boy like you
If you arc not wise you can never build a house
House building7
You have done well
As soon as you complete then I will come and watch over it for you
Ah Agya 1!
you are selling someone's own for me, how much more me
This one is pay back, you dont know why I am doing so
Agya you see here is not a store
Ahhhh
so let me give you 20 cedis for each
Eeiiii >«’’!!
35 cedis oo
NO NO NO "i
Ghanaians really want cheap stuffs
the price is 35 cedis why do you want to be like this
30 bags of cement
you have buy them 20 20 till it has finished
you know i'm the only one that buys for you
Oh don't be like that,
cheap things will always bring you into trouble
Father 20 is okay
That is even all of the money I brought (you give me 50)
25,25 = 50
Ah father I’m not new in this game oo
Is alright give it to me okay
Owura push and lets go
Father later okay
Come again incase of anything okay?
okay, okay
byee
AHH I!'
Twum Barimah where are they taking the cements to
They just bought it, 40 cedis
Bring the cement back here
where he is taking it to?
Thieves, is here a cement store
Oh don't talk like that here is a outside, are you a fooP
NO NO NO
so you are selling the goods of the one who gave you a place to stay 7
You are not ready to sell some for surviva
Me I'm not serious?
you are not seriuos to sell some
I'm not a thief like you are
Een, Comfort Armor
So if a dog is coming to bite you and there is my stick.
Won’t you use my stick on the dog
Is that what you saying
I'm asking that, a dog is about to bite you and there is my stick
would you let the dog bite and kill you
Twum Barimah you are a useless man
you are a very useless man
think a little before you talk
hrr bring it back you hear me?
take it away, it worth selling
It doesn't suit you, you are an elderly
So beheve as such
You hear ?
someone has given you a place to stay and you didn’t evendhankihim
but selling his items in the house
So you mean I shouldn't sell some of the items
I will tell him when he comes
tell him when he comes 111
tell him, tell him liar H
I will tell him when he comes
I will never shut my mouth
tell him Thieves has stolen all of them.
You' stole them
an older thieve, you stole it yourself
Thank you
Is not fine...
Foolishness, tell him when he comes
Lying woman
An elderly man like you
children are suppose to do this so you elderly will advice them
thief
If he is a wise man why didn't he stay in the house himself but me
And'does he gives me chop money for staying here everyday?
Twum Barimah
will he give me chop me? tell me
Twum becareful oo
Are you mad7
will tell him when He comes I!
Tell him
He will hear...
smoker, you parcel maunjuana as if you goin to sell but you smoke it all
Me a smoker?
then you laugh whiles you are asleep till morning, tramadol woman
Tramadol woman
J
p
•’'V.mVfe
Help me, who knows
maybe someone will help buy us some
so mummy, you are making Sandra also join you in this charcoal business
school is now out of her life
what do you want me to do?
Ahh?
what do you want me to do, you know the situation in this house,is it me?
what do you want me to do, you know tR5tsituatibn in this house,is it me?
ahh®.
a h±h?i
Is it my fault?
Sometimes I dont even Understand my father
If he had stop his smokings, we could have been in a better place by now
Wht do you mean 7?
Don't you know he caters for his first-son everyday?
Or don't you know the cigarrite is his first son?
He gives it chop money everyday
and ignores we the human beings
H m m m
Eeii Twum Barimah
What at all have I landed myself into?
Mummy
Is daddy intentionally doing this
ah what do you mean? that is wickedness, i mean that is very unpleasant
Eeii
he is a bad man i must sayz your father
HMMM...
So can he say we are his children some time to come in the future?
Hmmmm
As for me I won't cater for him in future not at all
all my plans are in my mind
I'm just .being cool with him now, i won't mind-him in future
I won't even let him know if i have something
(CLAPS)
CUT1
take the next scene for me
what scene is this
Is it scene two or ending of the movie around scene 93
Thank you
Eeii Comfort
What's your problem
My son said it that, you are just being friendly
But the movie
Who is directing and producing ?
who is directing this movie?
By all means, it’s Famous
If not famous then...
this movie might be Nakwaadus
Who is the marketing director of the Movie
the one who wants cheap stuffs
Adolf will market this movie
look, Comfort what have I done to you
that you have sat with my own children
and disgracing me to them
we are saying take care of your own children
thank you
A man who has be with you and have 2 kids with
and by doctors prescribtion I shouldn't work sake of my condition
so .1 am down today and everybody is disrespecting me
and you what did you say 7 you won't cater for me7
I won't say anything to you people
from today till your end you will never be succesful in live
Ahh Father
insults
Hey don't you .dare curse my children
paapa are you cursing us
I haven't curse you but I have cursed you
there are differences between the two
You will never be successful untill I'm dead
Look at him
( this one is a curse I'm giving-.to you)
Where did your music career get you
oh clear off my head
Your first track killed your whole family
Paapa was the music a tear gas?
It was more than a poison
whose song is this !!H
whose song is this1!*
whose song is this!!
whose song is this1
everyone died, that was when you couldn't play hit song again
I tell you, Iraq boomb is even small
singing!!1
this song will kill you after listening
she couldn't even be a star
congratulations
GOD will punish you
Thank you
you hear me
God will punish you
God bless you guys
look at him
GOD bless you
if only you are okay with it then we talk about it
please If you take your left, the room is the last one
Laughs.,7
So you can go and che’ck
therrlet me check and come
OH okay —^
ï»¿
Hrrr, Micheal Jackson
. Hrrr, Micheal'Jacksoh
Sc?don't you know you have to excuse,me7
So don't you know you have to excuse rme?
Ah i;h
why Ah what do you .mean by ^H! 7
But 1 am doing Ironing '
No you dont have manners
You are mannerless
4 you had to use your- brains and excuse 7^ us sake of thefvistor whO/iT'lrere- ’
you had to use your brains and excuse us sake of the vistor who is here
I have never come across anybody •who is disresoeGfful'hl<eyou
Mmmm ?
Is not your fault
but my family's
as how they have dissappointed me with the money/bsent to them, to .build a house
Ohh we know you these people, everyday you have been dissappointed but its never true
Me disrespectful7, I'm disrespectful like you as you have put,two risky in your hair
Mine is on my lips
Off it or else you will burn my,House
You don't know the price of a cement bag, off the iron!!
You doriJCknow the priceupf^a cement bag, off the irSn!!'1
Animal, look atihim
laughs..
Ermm how do you.see it
Ohijit's okay, I have^ta^en it
OH it's okay, I have taken it
ï»¿
Laughs...
Yea you are now doing business with me
so lets quickly deal with the money issues, if only you brought^
Oh I only came to do enquiries so there is no money on me
But the money is ready in the first place
we don't do that in kumasi here, you had to bring the money alongside with you
So you pay after inspecting the room
so what if I give the room to another person as soon as you leave
when anyone comes tell them its already been rented
No please, I do not do it like that.
First come, first serve
That one is straight dp
oh okay then I'm going to make preperations and come back
I get you okay
So^I thank you and_will like to take my leave-
Oh its fine don't you worry
bye bye
I will’b^expecting you
oh yes-please’I will come
Okay
he is a fresh guy but we can't use him for anything
Mmmm ”
MmrrTm 11
I'm dying^oub o? hunger, you’have kept for long
Eeei I'm feeling)hurYgry
I’ have been tired sake of this fufu
m m m
1 h'aVe been drunk already so it will be nice with.'theVufu
All you need is chilled water
laughing....
ï»¿
why are^you breaking it
whj are you breaking it
breaking what.Kop Fori
where is the fufu7
I didn't "get some oo'
a o ® !i g‘et s©m@’O©l
The<poun'der is not feeling well so theT&fu didn't come on today
so what did you think I'm taking all the shots for
ah so ^qu were drinking -sake of the food7
' no i was drinkinglto gb^and bath
yiee, it is'finish for us
finish for you and’who, your legsrather
f^o*
o
Eeii Anhwere, welcome we'lcbm'e a - v •
Eeii Anhwere welcome welcome
How are things going
Oh everything is fine Twum Barimah
since I helped you with the direction...
has the landlord confronted again 7
How would he...
How would he come there again
laughs...
He hasn't been there again, he can't even look at his own house when passing
He is not happy
I told you after doing the directions for you he can't even face you
Ah’
He can’t even enter the compound
Thank you so much
You understand?
You said it !1
how could I have survived here ?
How could I take good care of a place and being sack later to rent a room
would be a fool to acept that
you are hard as a rock
we are goin to share it
If its four, we share it two two
if its five, you take three, I take two. that is the new thing
Thats how it is suppose to be (AHH)
And that stupid Koo Fori guy
I gave you a direction and you didn't do it now that you are been sack away
And He came here ranting, And I told him I could slap him for what he is saying
You should have slapped him
You should have slapped him, Koo Fori is very foolish
Hmm
As if he is an animal
He is senseless
as I am in Ghana here and sombody will come from abroad and build a house
At new site
and then I stay there for you
for the place to modinize
and then you show up to take it
will go by all strengh to take the house
will come to you whenever I'm in hard times
will help you snatch peoples house for good
I second you
last time Yaw Baah
Yaw Baah ^^ which yaw baah
oh Kumah's son Yaw Baah
ah Yaw Baah who lives just here
I had an issue with him
Een "
i was trying to snatch his house but he caught me
so we have issues between us
That Yaw'baah wanted to kill you?
Yes Yaw Baah himself, I never knew he worships idols
I had a dream and in it I saw myself in shrines
And I said someone is trying to kill me
Een "
I said nothing
Not knowing it was him
Yaw Baah
he went to Akomadan
Kwaku Bonsam
is there where Yaw Baah went7
kwaku bonsam had almost finished everything
he slotted sheeps and poured libation
and mentioned my name but remembered to take a look at my picture
Ql • Ij/Jd;)!^ J^\l ' "	’
jjyafsjJ
as soon ^ r ^ s'; si
’“• qre
he shouted and said, eeii this fraudster? I'm even searching for him
As in you (laugh)
I'm powerful so he couldnt kill me
I have fraud him before
so Yaw Baah wanted to finish you if not you been powreful
yes h'im and kwaku bonsam
but havent you give kwaku bonsam's money to him
NO NO I will even kill him
Kwaku bonsam
Yes !1
get out!!!!
oh young man take your time
oh show some respect
landlord moving,them'out-as Twum/barimaH disagrees
ï»¿
look, man J*was ;hungrcy ,tha“t is why 4*sold the item?*
look, man I was hungry that is why I sold the items
As for you I dont want to hear a word from your mouth
would have pardon the woman and the kids but as much as you stay toghter, i cant help
that is why we arebeggihg^you
Argueing '••! H. ,
Fighting !H
Fighting !!>,
Fighting !H.
Fighting ’’•
Fighting ML <
Fighting >H
Bra kwame what is really going on
whatare you^reaHy .insenuating7'
I went to the house
and Gospi told me
you have sold the house to her
so doryou believe 1 can sell the house. to*Gospi
and do you even think Gospi has money to a buy a house
ernn 7
she called me last time
that you came there and started an arguement
what is that suppose to mean
And*I said okay, she should feel free >four saying that
Beacuse <or me Udon’t like all these arguementations and all that
this is^no big deal to worry me about this morning
you must be joking
you are the one telling her
the one who came to beg for a place to stay
you arc tcljing her to feel free for saying that
so you are giving her grounds on which she can claim ownership Tn the future
how can she claim*ownership * w -
as for me hdon'^t like too much.issues,and noise
so I saicbokay when she.said that, for it touring peace
so what is the»mcajnng of you making rioise about this
errn p
Akonno;-you are my .sister
you know I can't.selbthc house without letting you know
and after all if I have sold it, what really can you do7
that lady is someone's royal, so let her have her peace why all'these noise everyday
why?
You are playing with issues
you are making things bother me
Bra kwame becareful
be very very careful
if you were you just saying that for saying sake
and you are backing her to say that
then go
and let her know better that you were just playing with her
do you hear me?
Akonno let me tell you, that gurl is someone's daughter don’t worry her
is good for Her- also'to find a place to sleep
why is it that always you imake tog much noise about tftis,let-henfeel free
ï»¿
Mmm
Akua Gosp
I like sweets in my mouth, not only my mouth but my whole body
This is Gospi Gospia Gospias
chupa chucks with club
Its only me, if you don't nderstand go and hug transforner
that is my back case
since 1931
Eeii sister Gospi
Gnd afternoon
ahhhh Kwasi
I don't like that
don't call me sister Gospi, get angry when you call me that
call me Gospi and let me respond
alright Gospi
"ay niyTiame-..
*^Y .rename
fresh boy
okay I'm going to town, will be back soon
oh hold on
I wanted to ask you something but since you are here let me .make it quick
why, don’t you like the ampesi I did yesterday
oh is not like that,
but Ampesi is something I have no interest in
oh okay, but you could have let me know
ypu want something with soup?
as you can see
ahh that is why you have build this way
laughs...
don't worry at all
today I will get you some fufu hope you are okay with fufu
**••-
0^0
♦ d
^ < 4 * •
why ? do you feel bad ?
Oh not really but..
will give you some light soup with all kinds of meat
with some.ingriedients
do you prefer cocoyam or plantain
oh plantain will be fine
plantain, you want more iron right7, its not bad
but should .1 add some okro meat7
what is that7
okro
Okro will make it easy for you to swallow
you get it
yes but-the thing is, dont really have much on me so if only we can hold on
Akwasi I'm a town girl, looks like you playing with me Gospi
I'm a show girl,hands go hands come
kumasi girl like me how can I request, for money before I can serve my man
for whatU1!
I wil use my own pocket money
to serve you the fufu
so that when you also get money
you will also make me feel the cash
you shoot me with the money
you see the vibe?
don't worry at all, will let you feel the fufu
don't be.afraid at all
so when you come back will serve you at my place after your shower
so after everything then
soM'ishould come to your room for the food?
where else do you want you eat it ?
please don't make the work tideous
beacuse I can't cross the barrier to your end
so you cross then come'after everything then we add the John 3:16
onaapo then we do it like that, you get me7
okay, i get you
©3^3^^^^^	2.
willl you enjoy the toffee
oh naa
oh enjoy some for me
you won't enjoy toffee
will be back okay?
it will help you with the anaconda game
I will ride you roughly
he is really cute
RANTING....
Eciifthank you, thank you
Eeii thank you, thank you
Have you seen how the tiles is been designed?
Eeii Eei Eei
Young man GOD bless you
may GOD give you long life
Amen amen
GOD should'help you guys always so that we will find a place to sleep always
Oh may GOD give you long life
GOD bless you too
Amen, Amen
if you play your cards well,a time will come you will be a landlord by yourself
oh as for me I have been trying all my life it couldn't work out for me
I don't think I can build one now that I'm about to die
everything is possible for GOD to do
victory always comes in the end
•-' OH OH
look, let me tell you one thing
This house is for my niece
oh so is not for you?
no I'm building for my niece
But where is yours ?
oh where you came the other time
ahhh!H oh
ofcourse ofcourse
that is my house too you understand
but he is^n'ot in town
he stays in Germany
small small
the reason I brought you here is to weed and jeep here clean and tidy
for here to be^jean and nice
all the time
don’t worry, how can I stay in such a nice house and not keep here clean
If we talk about care takers across the country
I am the king of care takers since I started life
I am the president of care takers,
Because I started as a kid and I have been like thTs^since then as a care taker
untill we are here as you are giving me this house
soj'm a king in it
I have introduce a lot of people into this work
really ??
I havej^romote some people
wooow
yes I have people if you want, I will let therrrcome stay in there for you
so asffor that, I'm the king
but now you are no more part of care takers
Hmmm
because if you do goods unto others, others will do good unto you
If you be a good person to my niece, that is all.
there wouldn't be any problem
ofcourse
the houe) can even be yours
ofcourse it will be mine III!
what7
it will surely be mine by all means
take your-time father
by all means it will be
I beg you take good care of here
have you seen how close me and your is
I don't like the way, they were treating you out there
okay
some gave me a house earlier on
there was nothing in the house
he had to think about us
is there a bed in there7
No there is no bed
but you have a bed bring it when you coming
as for my bed really
its blocks that i have arranged in a bed form with wood on top
really?
I can't carry all that here
I will see what I can do
let me show you the rooms
Is that how you guys are ?
-Gospi!!
Gospi H
Is that how wicked you are??
you have rented the room's to people in this house
you have rented the rooms to people in this house
that is good of;you
that:is very go'dd you
whemyou collected the money
you want-company
and you brought a whole team here with you
you could have continue the other house at the*B“ack
so we could even consider that, atleast you have brought some progress in house
Gospi where is the money you collected from them?
Don't even think of saying you\ ^ have given the money to my brother
I beg you find another excuse
because I just spoke well my brother
he is the one who sent me here
he said he hasn't.even hear from you
he doesn't even know of you giving the rooms for rent
so Gospi, if you are thinking of^aying you have giving the money to'my Brother
please find another excuse
find another excuse because, it didn't work
whatever or however you Gall yourself
is this a breaking news
what news paper is this'the head line of
which station is^this the headline
what news are they reading
and you are.coming to destroy my eardrum
Bird like you
insults
you are making noise
lady, let me tell you for you to listen
you know already that I came to stay in a thick forest
you know the struggles I have been through
and hard prayers
fasting
I have been through all-kinds of pastors for directions
I have been through all kinds of pastors for directions
I have been through allkinds of pastors for directions
So today, here is now a better place which has attracted you
It has been attractive so you are rushing like a fresh fish from the sea
so you are coming to do what?
I have given it for rent and so what ?
let me tell you
do you know how many properties people have taken from owners for free in kumasi here
do you know peoples houses, i mean mansions
Lands
cars
I mean properties that has been snatched from their hands
been snatched from-their hands
proverb...
whatever you call yourself
let me tell you that me Akua Gospi I'm too risky
let me tell you that me,
so becarefull in the path you want to lead me to
I beg you please (claps)
I'm clpping for you
Gospi understand, what I’m about to say
those who has their property been snatched
they want it to be so for people to take it
because maybe them going to the north was a total waste
but as for us
laughs
you can never take it today and tomorrow too
so if you think
the juju you have done
maybe it worked on my brother, but as for me, never
So Gospi, don't you think you on a firm
ground,because you shaking so find a differnt place
hahahahaha
I thought you were gonna say you are a northener
You just went there7
you went there for nothing
I will salute'you if you were to be one of the northeners
because as for them, I I respect them ajot
lady
I have been through hot waters,not cold ones '
I have been through hot waters,not cold^bnes
the tree you want to climp is very slippery
becareful so you don't break your head, you hear me 7
becareful
here is peaceful
what brings you h'ere'
I'm facing some challenges
you will face
I need help from you
4“
my landlord is moving me out of the house
care-takers will stay in someone's house for a .long time for thereto be-attractive
care takers will stay in someone's house for a long time for there to be attractive
and then they sack you just before they complete the house
and^then they sack you just before th^y complete'the-house
so I discussed it with a friend of mine
and he directed me here
he first directed me to baaba
ah Baaba don’t have a room
Baaba bragged to me that he is the only one that can get me some, but he couldn't
for girls is what he has been doing around, hmm
for*girls is what he has. been ''doing .'around, hmm
so I had to run^and come talk to you first
so I had to run and come talk to you first
so you find some for me
and I have even find out that, I can even get a room at this your place
and I have even find out that, I .can even get a room-at'this your place
here is full, my children can't even find a place to sleep
oh okay
father please help me because my th'ihgs’are^Stside
father please help me because my things are outside
the weather is even cloudy, you will be a dead man if it rains
how many are they for it to be whip by rainfall
as for here
you are right of what you sying
you .are right of what yousying
itit’been a long'time since we^rnet
you are right about what you are-saying
you are right about what you are saying
as for room
as 'for room
it's only me that can help give a room as ^a’care taker
if you bypass me nobody can get you you one
I'm the only almighty
everyhouse that a care taker is in, I am the ,6ne that gave to him or her
because since my child hood, GOD created me in such a way that-I-can't build a house
As for me I think you have build your own
oh no no, I'm I fool, someone should build so I will come stay in
You gave baaba's place to him too.
yes I gave it to him
Eeii^but Baab.a said he is even .the one who gives others some
©hdbn'bmind baaba he is insane
how is ypur wife
I'm not married
Me too I’m not married, we all dating
because marriage is difficult these days
people don't like it sake of the court endorsement
because will be a fool to bring someone's daughter to building like this
No, I will marry if I complete my own house
ï»¿
so you won’t even sit
no I can't sit
because I'm in hot waters
what is it, is your mother dead7
That one will even be a good news
that is true, funeral is very profitable these days
yes
which work will give you 10,000 Cevery month
some will get profit-
and some will also lost Heavily
what is the matter
father
the man I'm in his house as a care taker
that man is really stressing me
he won't let i* e have my peace of nind
he doesn't want to let me have my freedom
you being the one helping him 7
he is still misbehaving
he comes there everytime like his office
you know it's rainy season,
I always weed but because of that the weeds grows quick
but this man won't understand and will be talking rudely to me
he even wakes me up every morning to come and sweep
ohhhhh "I Africa specially Ghana, some people rush too much
some landlords are really disrespectful
there is nothing like this abroad
no no
unless Ghana
that is why we' will also wild to snatch the house
huh!
someone is helping you in your house, and you are misbehaving Edwards l^r
he is not letting me have my peac-e
you won't even take it to-your grave
someone will even take itifrom free
don't have anybody to go to father
what is your problem7
father, because i have nobody to talk to
and you are the elderly in this neighbourhood so I decided to.dome
maybe you can be of help
maybe you can even find me a new place
I don't even know what do
as if I'm in a mechanic shop
but where is your father?
my father7
he went to lybia a long time ago he hasn't return
Gadaffi’s death has really affected some people
he might be deadlight-.
the way it is it,can be*so
before GOD and man
I'm doing this for you sake of you are a woman
would have sack you if you were to be/a man
GOD specially created woman, there some things on you
that makes us feel better when we touc-h you
parts of our body can make us give you guys cars and after that you will be sad
I’s just seconds
and now I’m an agent who collects a little for chop money
and you being a lady by all means I will help you
look all your troubles are over
the house will be yours forever
is it true7
I will let the house be yours and he will also come to you to beg for chop money
whiles the house belongs to you
Ecii Agya Twum
don't worry about anything, I will give you a direction
I hear
feel free when you sleep
I hear thank you very much, so when should I come
OHHHHH”
You will make a mistake when you rush, take your time
E rn n!
don't run or else you will fall and make a mistake
by all means I will make the house yours
You hear me7
I have heard you father
thank you
I trust you father
feel free when you sleep
God bless you father
I will come early in the morning father
from today to....
just soon
I will call you soon
I have heard .you
will come early tombrow morning
I have to come early'so'you can help me
don't wb'rr(y,
God bless you father ( GOD blessyou too)
look at buttocks
playing like a tennis ball
playing like an intrument
like that of roman c-atholic's instrument or methodist
OH my GOD, GOD really created buttocks
You have really done well
if you watch over someone's property well, the owner will always be happy
I'm also thankful
Yaa stop, madam is coming
you are doing it yourself today
yes mom
you have done well
madam this is where I was begging you
that lets use this sand
there is cement already, if only the mason's will come then we finish portion
mm mm
sake of the erosion
I made my mind that when they working on the upperside then they add it too
but for the ground, sake of the frequent rainfall you have to weed always
I weed it oo but
it will always come up after a heavy rainfall
ï»¿
so I made my mind that if
so I made my mind that if got something I will spray it
because it always comes up easily
ernn I think that one will be better
so all of it could die
but is Yaa not a student?
who7
Yaa’
Oh he goes
hmmm madam
is not easy
they vacated and resumed
and vacated again
so things was complicated
is alright
eeni madam
I understand things are not easy these days even for people like us
so anytime he is ready to go call me I will help okay
Eeii GOD bless you mom
GOD bless -you so muc-h
It's okay don’t worry
okay so let me give you the money if you will buy the weedicide
\ .A :. ^Hr
. * I
^
5.
• * ^
I have also tell the mason, the foreman will also
Sandra you have a nice place, here is really nice
Hmm this one even a someone else's
ein this one too is for somebody?
what is really happening to you guys
life is really teaching us a lesson
Sandra this has got nothing to do with life
this is the time you have to do something
ï»¿
you have to help yourself
you arew still there waiting for your dad to do something for you.?
sister
you faher has nothing for you
you have to wake up and do something
all these hot ladies around don't get help from any family but struggles themslves
sister for me where do i get help
It's all my effort
ofcourse you really looks nice
look at all thses jewelleries you wearing and even your hang bag
that is why I'm telling you
this the time you have to hep yourself your father will do nothing for you
why don't you believe your father cannot help you
you have eveything as a woman
look at your breast, your butts and your beautiful legs
what is it men can't do for you
sister help yourself
help yourself!!
that is exactly what she is telling you, be wild
that is exactly so, be wild
if you don't make wild they will overtake you
even the mouse is wild stealing things
the cut is also wild catching mouse
what of you human
God helps (those who areisenous
Ikife is what you have build not that of your father's
that you want to take
If I have a house is not for you alone
is for you and alllyour siblings
everybody will give birth and it will'turn to a.family house
build your own!!
build your own
insults is what you like throwing7
□ necessary things
unless you didn't see
always insulting
here in I have brought you to, you stil want me tyo cater for you still
here in I have brought you to, you stil want me tyo Ster for you still,
I should still work for you to eat, ;for what^reason7
I should still work for you to eat, for what reason7
and you are insulting me
' look at'your’bwn friend
she said you are wasting yourself
donlt rely on me
I won't help you
I won't help you!!! I
I won't help you!!!!
you are refering to her nice cloths and praising her
you arc refering to her nice cloths and praising',heT
have you seen^how embarrassed you are
Insults
she even crying
you don't look'good when you c-ry
this is your end
if you hate, you hate me in vain
if you hate me, you are not God
vbu hear me7
this thing, is 'even/okay
lS Mb|j 0g @vlr ^ ^
look at how beautiful you are and and look at this thing
as for you, ohhh this my daughter is a fool
are you not beautiful than,her?
how can :thisjone be .too be richer than you
is because you don't respect
you, is your mother alive7
ï»¿
you take care of her?
yes I do
you give her money7
ï»¿
a®:5fflij»na»)
you haven't give me anything and you are insulting
hmm
thank you, you have really done w.ell
get away !!!
I even regret having you as my child
and I even get angry that I tried bringing you into this world
sometimes I even want to
give my manhood to somebody
for him to use it and bring it back to me later
foolish girl!1
ï»¿
what is your father implying?
I’m still here, what do you mean?
Sandra lets go and excort me
may GOD be with you
go and excort her for her to give you money so i could get some cigaritte
Ermm wello
M m m h u h
,- dim the biggest
I come in peace
piawwwww
you are my good frpend
yes
you know you have been through a lot and you are still surfering
I have suffered indeed
V ' yLI zj/3 ^yh.uj ^T^jySfevlJ
,th‘e person wants your success
I want to help you
if you want the house I gave you to be yours forever
and feel free when you sleep
so that your wife and family will also feel comfortable
please let me help you
if killing or anything follow me
I want this house to be yours
kill the landlord
and be the owner
elder
is that how your mind is
or get her insane
make her useless so the house can be yours
or else there will be a time she will sack you from the house
bsi^ ® ysiur nsim^y/jj
are you now going to go back to your hometown
your hometown is also a long destination
you were a fisher man
I thought you were a wise man sake of your age
you speak wisely words alone for kids to listen
how old I’m I? has it reached heaven?
do you lose your mind when you are growing
don't you know, from 100 years going your mind turns to that of children7
yours hasn't turn to that of todlcrs don't force it to be so
wickedness
there is no landlord who has even given me money for working in a house before
but she gave me money to buy weedicide and even bought a machine for the spraying
she has given me money to buy cement
for the work
she is even connecting light so that she can buy television'for us
should I go and kill such a person for the house'?
what is wrong if you kill him
a person who has worked her heart out abroad for her house
I should go and kill her for it7
but didn't you also struggled before you got this place
what?
didn't you struggled to come stay here
since you are not the owner, it can never be yours
so what do you mean?
I beg you, I can't kill someone for her property
so you won't do right?
you won't right
if I will do
would have given you a better answer
you 'don't deserve money, It doesn't'fit you, you are useless
it doesn'tifit me?
I will stay in my poverty than to kill and be successful
if I am healing you and you don't want me to
I'm going with my drug
take it 'and go
I beg you
I'm the one that find this place for you
so I want my fee
my thousand Ghana cedis
what did you do for that makes you deserve thatkinda money
I told you that if I get the house for you, you v/ill thousand GH. cedis'
give it to me
and again
you being an ashanti
I know you will spread this issue
will kill you if^you do so
me?
ah man
we deal with laws in this country
are'always small but not the biggest
have you seen you have small brains?
you just have wicked mind
what are you saying7
I have nothing to be'given to you
will use it for meat rather,
is that what you telling me?
how can I give my to a wicked man like you7
Fighting 11
ï»¿
^H C 0 0
G
Een
ï»¿
. f f» ‘ -"A-'’' ^-:^<
it's been a while
are you the one in this place7
yes I'm in here
Eeii
♦ •••
yes, I just'woke preparing to come and weed as I.saw someone standing there
not knowing it's you.
Yaa becareful or else you will hurt yourself okay
I beg you'
why have you landed here
my loandlord came, mean where I was staying first
he came to complete the place, so I had to^move out
so I went to see your own friend
who7
ah who do you think I am talking about
oh Twum Banmah
Eeii Twum BaTimah
Twum Barimah
Twum Banmah is really a barrier
what will we do if not him
He is really a good,person but.sometimes he over act in such a way which is way ward,
oh why 7
He told me if I only want the house it can be mine
ycss
everything is not for free
how can someone's building be mine
do I have money to buy this house?
he said he can take me to somewhere
and eliminate her for the^house to be mine
and I said is too much H
Twum !!
you never want to stop wickedness
I didn’t let him go scot free
Ahh >i
w h y
so you insulted him?
ahh I told him straight away
Yieeeee
what is it?
what is wrong with you7
when will you be a wise,man
Untill when will you be civilized
look, what is wrong with the issue Twum Barimah brought up?
what is wrong ;.with him telling you to be the owner of a house
what is wrong with him telling you to be the owner of a house
what?
it is very wise to do so-
let me tell you
I have told you before that we have to wash your brains at the car wash center
because you have dirt in your brains
this person,is helping you to have your own hbuseand you misbehaving
property like this7
your body and your dialougue.sounds the same
haven't you heard such before
why don't you guys have sympathy all
we don't even know what this kid does to survive, she has really tried to do this
she doesn't know me from anywhere
but she invited me in to, stay here so that I can prepare'myself
your friend has told me this and I'm telling you, you are here supporting him?
have you seen what you are wearing?
ohh wonderful
let me tell you
this world we are living in
if you don't be vigilant*
and use your sense to snatch things from people you own anything in this world
you are really surprising me
why do you have to be surprised?
you have really surprised me
for what reason
Yaa
Uncle!
have you heard some7
Hmmm
have you seen your uncle
Grown ass thief
say that again?
thank you
Yaa
you calling me a thief
Yaa do 1 look like a thief
ah but Anhwere I will be happy to sleep with a lion than to sleep with you
I won't even sleep with you sake of your shallow mind
listen to one thing, we are in a world where everyone is wild and ready to kill
I can never commit this kind of sin
what is wrong about what I'm telling you
because I fear God
nobody is going to Bel^we that you are the owner orf/tf^?!house
Ah for what reason?
do you even think that you deserve this house
why don't I deserve it
as you are standing there
find a chopbox and be the owner
Oboy aluu don't insult me
is okay, is okay
Jet me tell you this
don't say anything"
ohh 1 said don't say anything and you are still talking
ermm
don't let it out
hey!
woman
yes
ahha
why have you finsihed the*scwSbingrso soon
were following me when I was coming7
no I was surveying you
^T) (®) ^?7
so y0ur4ey.es are closed and can't see things
I'm wearing spetacles unless you take it off for me
I have glycoma in my eyes so take me to a-specialist for them to openatetfor me
before I can come check the toilet
then try and do it yourself because you have hands
A lady like you cleaning a toilet, you have to use detergent to.wipe»all the bacterias
but you have.done it anyhow like you want and leaving
if I hadn't come you would have gone right?
I will still go whiles you are here
you are here but I will still go
I have used detergent all kinds of it nature, you still saying it is smelling?
then go and get me folder water to scrub it for you
then come with your mat
after that bring your dinning table and come and eat here
haven't you seen that we have scrub the toilet?
or yours eyes are at your back that you can't see?
woman
it's in my noise
that is why
you think I'm soft ernn?
I'm not soft, did you even ask me what brought me here
have you asked me7!!!
It was the same thing at where I was staying in the first place
that is why I was moved
so woman don t'tr.y'
bec-ause you will regret itwvhen\ypu -rush
because you will regret it when you rush
you will never be happy
what??
go back1
Twill slap you with the broom, you will never'forget
I said go and buy me folder'water to scrub for you to come a nd \sleep there
een why?7
since I came here I have notice you are the one
Eeiii!! don't point the broom at me
I said go back .or else I will hit you with broom
since I came here have u sweep before
But I have been quiet all this while
you have never sweep in this house before
have you scrub the toilet before?
have you scrub,there before7
I have just been quiet, but^m -not that s *fC
are you talking to me?
I have just kept mute abouF^all your silly doings'
are you talking to me7
ofcoiTrse yes
then you are mad because you are telling me bullshit
I the landlord should scrub the.bath room? for you to .enjoy'with-your^Big-butts.
don't hiUme with the rubber,!!!
FIGHTING ’"<
Gospi, Gospia,Gospias
Allah
Koo Eon
ï»¿
Koo Fori
Koo FonU!
hate useless men
is that how we sleep?
with your eyes blinking like a toy, is that how we sleep
I slept deep
is over to you...
so Koo Fori you meanryou didn't hear what is going on
what?
didn't you hear that useless girl having arguements with me
I heard a noise out there-, but I taught it was some'kids
because elderly ones don't talk like that
didn't even think you are the^one
so it was you that she has insulting you like that?*
Insulting me??
eeii then you are in doom
^
oh shut up
what have I done to be insulted
let me weep for you
ï»¿
I didn't know this girl can insult like that
Koo Fori
weep for yourself
^' ,
you are being a useless elder staying in this house.
an elder have to encounter any trouble th'at-comes, so that he will address for peace
you are here relaxing like a sad dog
you had to call me When all the alligations sta®
although it's ladies fight but I could have join, afterall I'm fighting for mydandffi z .
but you didn’t alert me
so why are you blaming me?
you are very useless
next time when you hear me fighting with the lady come early and rescue me
you are my size so if she giyes-me pressure then I transfer it to you
barter traded V*. *
do you understand7
time of the fufu :isTe'ady, be fast and get me som^
I'm on heat
okay
I’m going for a stanter
Eeiii
I f you don't live you life well in this world people can talk to you anyhow
You couldn't even fight with your own mate,but me a man
if I touch you I have trouble
as for me Akua Gospi if you don't take care I will beat you with pressure
will beat you and then go to prison
Gospi
eeii
but
eeii Bra'kwame you have surprised me
should I offer you a*Ghair?
but why are you sleeping outside and not inside
you have really surprised me you didn't even call me
Hmm you know I seldomly comes here
I come only when there is trouble
but Akonno, how are^you doing-
I’m fine y
ï»¿
Bra kwame what brings you here this afternoon
My only sister that I cherish so much brought me here
My only sister that I Gh'erish so much brought me here
she has been worrying me that you have make this place a mess with all kinds of filty
but I haven't seen anything that shows as suc-h
Hey!! Bra Kwame what are you saying7
why-areryou trying to-eliminate yourself from the issue
haven't you seen here.is not tidy?
look-at where cldths,are hanging
the?e are' people'staying h'ere
they will do washing by^all means and dry them, where to you expect them to dr.y
Okay so when are you going to complete the house for us to move in
why are you talking as if you are controlled by batteries
are controlled by batteries
He said my house didn't you hear him
Bra" k wa m e Ih av.e .y'o u |h e a rd ;■ h e r?
listen to her whenrshe speaks ah
relax and listen
Gc/ociness
Bra a kwame
" ♦' 'f
0^
I said when are you completing the house for us to come in
rigfft now'we have to moyeiin
for the house issue relax is not a rush, you know one step at tioTe
But is alright me and Gospi will com'e sit-xdown,
y.ou and who?
Gospi, Gospia; Gospias
I am his advisor
chief advisor
I will sit down with him and plan everything
the money will come to me and buy everything
she that came to beg for a place to stay
Eeim sister
that is an abomination statement, I can fight with you if you say that again
so you are standing there for that gospi'tb beat me here right?
bra kwame bccarcful about what you are doing
that your hypocrite nature of yours is what I hate
he is just like you
is what you 'are saying the matter .we'discuss at home7
Gpspi, you know what, this time 1 don't wanna waste time
yes man
I will be on my way
een then let me excort Bra Kwame
excorting who, lets go
oh' don't worry yourself
oh Bra Kwame, anything for the boys?
anything for the boys....?
i'So^n't play with money issues
oh I will bring it later
brjng a little
so that I won't give it to anybody else
father I will brin'g’iitVon myvway coming
NO NO NO
Is a must to pay a little
«jW?
alright father
father then take this
okay okay
ofcourse later
thank youjfpr’the money
what money have you collected
he c-ame to rent a room
I know him from a very long time ago
late-Yaa bo‘.atengmaa"s grand son
he c-ame because he has no place to stay
so,he came and I have given him' somej for rent'
and he is going to; pay. later-when'.he comes
.which room?
the one1,we are in
have you .build any house
so-which room' are you talking about
ah this house we are living in, he is coming to sleep with* us
or you are going to give someone's chamber he gave us to him as rent7
be patient
comfort.
com fort-
Dont I give you your share of the money when I rent the room to people
Eii Twum Barima11
Those silly things that you did^; selling those propertiesdeading to our expulsio’h ,
But God being so good we have a new home now ,
you want to rent it outto people again
Do your-children evren have.a place to sleep 7
But he can sleep with us when he comes or ?
To sleep with who ? It's as if you have kerosene'in your brain.
How can we sleep in the same room with this grown-up man standinh here 7
Young man will you live in the room you are renting alone 7
@f course...! need my own room
Oh but you didnt tell me that .
wife and I
That;is why ^requested three hundred ’Ghana Geo is fdrjthe whole ye'ar.
If^so 'then I will ^collect my money back
Ecen so you want your-,own room for just thf^cThundreo GPiana Geclis Z
But' hvow can I live with you inrthe same room 7 ( politely)
^^^2lZ!^	, Oa^w^^ be stupid I must say
Give me my money-then !
And you Comfort...! wonder what kind of marriage material you'are
And you Comfort?..! wonder whaC. kind of marriage material you are !
[ What ? Qh leave alone ]^ d’
God will surely'punish you I tellj^ou
Young man collect youc/noney and leave,.here [Agya give me my money] ■
Agya no no no Pwon't understand'
Listen ! listen
I have subtracted consultation fee , sitting
fee as well as a fee for entering my house for fifty Ghana Gedis
Agya I wont understand because’this is not in law gi^nTe my money/'
Why । noU?
Give me my money !
[Collect your money-and leave ijere
[Singing]
Hey !!! man [ Eeeiii ]
®h wow! It's been a long time I came here ooo. [Yes ooo Madam]
You've really done well on this farm !!
I will cultivate .all of this area too
O'hYwow ! wow > you've really done well [Yes oo Madam]
‘But/please when the maize is mature please give me some to cultivate [Qoooool1 h]
You neecTmaize eer 7
Yes ooo 1 You've made cultivation so interesting to* me
[Yieee’ee J^icfr^^ odo']
Okay I've heard you
®h when you are leaving ; I have one plantain standing there
ifegot mature just last three days
L wjll giyelit-to you if will^e edible by-the
time you arrive at wherever- you are going
.But howJsjUT&ssible'/p^ edible by/t'Ae'time IVget:hvom£ P-vA
.Sure1.'1! it-;Will
'Sure '• it will *	•	1
Yo.u've^really done well, flay God’bless you
That is what I.say everyday’that when someone puts spmetmhg iny/odr
care and you'are able^to Aeep^iLsafe., the person always tha’nk'fuh
Thank You!
out ofT^h;g6o\dfcie‘eds
I'm ver^/If ap py at • hovv’h a nd y o u ’ v e1 w b r k e d t o /a*c h' i e v e * t Id i s
It's not in ,ydur house only that I'.ye been able to achieve this
I've lived in.many h'ouses.and J'.thipk you are unique in^the way ;you-treat-people'
Please if you come-and thingsjare/io'Ui'n xndef <tell me [ Don't iwprryjl' ve’K’ea r^you;]
I really like the way^hings are Please continue th'isTway !
SdH)^ J ^ j Sli •
i - « • ^JT
the masons will start work tomorrow
So I wantetorgiveyou n/oney, sp-thaUypy take care^of their needs v/he"n’-.t'heV\GorY^
Has Yaa^gone^tojschooi*
Oh-y.es
She says they are doing Home Economics 'today and
you Gan imagine the things
I gave her yesterday ; some mature maize
But is maize included in the things they are to ser?d forWe practical ? [Oh yes]
® h ® kay !!
So give ithe^masons two hunS're^Gh'ana cedis
when they come and keep tPie rest for yourself
But please how many are they ?
if^ey'are four
Eeei Madam...'why all these expenses 7
But .four pep'ple are exoected to do:such work or ?
No... employ-only one of them y I'will do the^ot} d7f the oth'er thretyrriyselK
But how)Gan you do that 7
Once I pick up the^shov.cl’-; I will do it [Laughs].
Look afKimH!, -
Nobody thinks you,can do-what you do when'they see .your-stature;
W h y • h a ye yp u ‘>vp r ny’t w d*';', trousers at the sam’etfime ?‘
®h y^es.-.a lot of pickpockets are arpundhso I have to protect myself
So I beg of you continue your good works [d've heard you]
park well so I will see you
but madam don't you like leafs?
(No I donlt)
Oh okay I hear
Eeii! *
borga borga
en Akonoba for real
- you feg^suc-h a bombastic
Eeii (come on)
Bogi1! thank you anyway
where is Gospi?
why (is) she not there?
I have been looking everywhere since I came
wasn't she there when I was leaving?
maybe I will see her outside
but is she relate to you guys?
H m m m
you have really asked a question
I 'don't Ing® this lady
anywhere ^ this world
since my brother started this house
and she came to plead with us to get her a p-lace to live
and I was like, how could you stay in a house that hasn’t been roofed
she said no, we should let her come in
so we let her in, as a care taker
and this is it
so this house is not for Akua GospP
does she have a peny to build a house7
Eeii you too-
eeiiii
Eee but can you take someone's property just like that?
the'house is not for'her?
does she have a peny to build a house?
look at the kind of amout' she'collected us?
what7
she collected us money7
she gave here to you as a rent7
yes fry©) rent?
I just needed a five star hotel when i came but she said here is cool
but she gave us this long list of rules since I entered
I hust had^c-alm down
what kind issues is this7
she really collected you m£ney before she gave here to you7
yes she did
with all sort of rules and regulations
ï»¿
do you know,
I have no idea abo'iut it7
she has never 'done ghg/aGCOunt to anybody
I see....
Hmm
I will be back<^
you mean she has been spending the money without your concern7
then you have to be careful
naa I need to see her
you leaving just like that7
Yaa
what,are you sleeping there for?
uncle I'm feeling sleepy
then'go to the room and sleep
Uncle is very hot in there
Eeeim fat girl
o'h no
she is mor;e than a pregnant woman
ah
always asleep
knock in
Eeiiii, man
I greet you father
i gG.et. uu_idi >t
1 6?
the one on the ground7
yes' please
oh the owrfer.iS'abroa’d and not i'n Ghana \^
ph the, owner is abroad and not in Ghana V	■ 'v„^i, '•	>
oh he is abroad
oh I came we have agreed on terms about a room, so I came to pay the advance
young man
have you thought about the one you are renting from7
father as^for me I don't know
I couldn't-argue when he saicf it's.-his house
Eeii until when are you gonna let people stop bullying you
father you can’t predict on anyone sake of how he isdbokihg or what he is wearing
hejioesn't have a peny, he is a Gare taker like me
he is a bully
that is why he has persuaded the landlord to snatch the house from him
ï»¿
you are shouting7
and you have the guts to come here to pay the money to him as landlord
are you a kid7
then I havestopped
uncle stop this is not your fight
he is not a la nd I lord
he’s never bought a block before
how many years was he giving it to you
please I wanteed 3 years
3 good years
he would have let you forget ab'out everything in three days
your GOD has«really saved you
even my little niece here won't even commit the mistake you were about to commit
/. BHB !t -M» / ^“ " ■'<■ ,,	•'
■t < '!• !! !!!! I. *“ !! !!!■ //	0.
uncle don’t seek*tnouble for yourself, .this iSxnobyourJfight
thank you father
, don't thank nrre^goH
you must be controversial.
yes, my uncle can be
Gospi
say my name for me
upon the second thought
I'want to come and live in this house with you
don't like the current place I'm in now
so,I'm coming to stay in this house with you all
so you want to tell me, you wanna stay here with us?
why so?
that is what I just said, I don't like my current residence
please is your brother sick dr he has lost his phone
I don't need my brother's permission before I stay here
because'.what is my brother's is mine too
so I said
•ty^'f^- * '^r^L'Ham^ommg to stay here
ï»¿
1 can observe-proceedings myself
you are coming to observe proceedings
woman let me tell you
you’ brother is aware of a"ny room I rent to people
I give him the money intact without taking a pony from it
ï»¿
%■$'
'fe^^^f^V00 t° understand is
what I want you to understand is
your brother is the senior coach
antf^'m the’assistant coach sitting on bench looking at what is happening on pitch
so\yoirhave to communicate with'.your brother
so if your brother order me to let anyone in, I will just do that
I'm ever ready
I'm taking orders
you understand
-spdf you-feel like I'm talking shit
police department wasn’t built in yam
the police are not wearing the black in vain
central police station is even the biggest
the prison is even closer, so you can be easily jailed.
^y^uVzarvsend me there
^yoihcan send me there
;so they should serve me imcourt, and I will come and deliver
if you say so
what' I want you to understand is
we have planned that already
and afferthat meeting, it came to an end that, we are the owners not the beggers
so if you are the coach or whatever
w.e-are the owners of the team
ir'V? Jj/^ir^'^ *	• •	•
who stays arid who leaves
sb look around and find a room tlnat is big and fits me
and give the person in
it's morrey to; Him or her because I'm coming
err woman
you said black stars is yours7
>^VpMsaid?l^^ stars is yours?
countGy/ma'h sohko or whatever will tell you
that blaekstars is for Ghanaians
fire burn you all
you are staying up there and spending all tFie cash as the boys are suffering
'ty*>'iWi -~'
why didn't you occupy the place when it was at it poor nature
and Akua Gospi has occupied
I weeded and made here a better place
and now here is a better place so you want to come for it
re burn you lady
ï»¿
V^rnore fire ’ • w.
. - I ifev^4rhore fire
^W/M^'
.'’^^’^'•' ^ * V - f i re
Thunder
strike you
you understand
this is your last warning okay
errm Afua Gospi
per what is going on
is either
you stay with me or you leave if you are not-comfortable with the rules
because as you are saying that this?place' was full of reptiles
it,was the same as you insisted us to let you in here
here is better now, so,humans needs to occupy so I'm coming
y.ou are’coming to stay with us
so I was an animal per what you are saying right?
ernnn7
then you will come and meet the animals here
then you come and play with the animals like cows
i,7you hear me?
a'cheek of it!
we are ready to deal with you too
ahww
I will pretend I didn't hear
even if I heard it, you must be joking
so Gospi or what so ever
if people don't know who you really are as for me I know
Eeeiiii! > •
what do you mean by that!!!
what dp you know about me
what k‘ind person I am?
who has really stole»all the sand?
Twum!!
Twum!
Twum!11
who is it?
Eeeiii chairman
Oh then come inside
To do what?? come outside let me show you something
oh please then lets sit down for*a while
Twum we won't sit come let me show you something
Twum why??
why why
look at how someone have stole half of the sand I brought
who did that7
errr my nephew, is not arm robbers-
I went into financial crisis
I had nobody to’ turn to so I sold Have of if
Ah Twum!11
ah Twum why!!!
you didn’t add money when you gave me the house
I couldn't be a thief when the crisis came?
I had to sell some of it to survive
so as I was selling then train too was also'taking part away
so please you don't have to blame me this way
I don't like what you are doing
1 can't afford given you a house and at the sme time sell my items
we don't do it anywhere
people does that.but you don't wanna do it, some even add women
but for me, I don't worry people that much
and I want truth because i'm grown
a lot of people don't want the truth
what would you do if I said I know nothing about
you don't want the truth
I sold it
you could have use the blocks over there to block the drainage
so the rain will not take it away
don't you ever touch the sand again from now unwards
please I have heard you
I brought it here for a purpose
consider the friendship we have
and I respect your wife a lot
that is why I'm doing this
please don't repeat this again (oh I won't)
you are an elderly
and I don't want it to be a huge a matter
ok ok
calm down, calm down
ï»¿
I have really done well,
I was in India when I built this house
really
Oh yes hwas in india
that was where I brought m'oney fo them to builod thisWouse for me
oh then you have really ^one wll
they are even two
I even have one at the back there
father the house is really fine
but please the house is very weeddy, so please take a look at it so you weed for me
ofcourse I will, I have even started weeding it
I have told those people to'come and spray here, I don't know why they not here
why do some Ghanaians play with their jobs this way
is okay don't worry, I will be on my way but please let them come fix the ligRts
have even ordered the electriians to come and do it
how much did you want me to pay
Thousand cedis, I haven’t complete so I have reduced the prices
hey!! hey!! HEY!!!
Foolish boy
what money have you given to him?
I'm renting a room here
Hey
Anh were what you arc doing in this area will bring trouble to us someday
youngman
are you a kid7
ahhh?
will y,ou give this house tor rent for thousand cedis if it were to be yours?
Agya why is he talking like this7
I'm asking you a question
do we give such a place for rent7
father bufthis is the landlord
who is the landlord7
you are young so you are shallow minded
I wonitsit back and watch you do somthing that won't help you in the future
Hrr-he-is-a care taker!!!
ah father is that how you are??
Hrrrr
you are a child
hrrr g o and collect your money
No no give me my money, I can't rent.again
FIGHTING
give me my money, you don't even deserve to be the owner of this house
Give me the money
my 20 cedis has mistakenly joined yours
what7 come on leave here
ah father you have really done well
oh youngman
come for this money
he would have bully me
I will give you to MF so they help you out
don't come here again, and tell your colleagues too
nowadays don't give their houses to care takers
thank you father
herrr oboy alloo!!
so you have really done this to me
oh clear off foolish man
I will deal with you
come!!!!
exchanging words
yes
you are coming?
eeiii!!
this ending7
but Abena, sometimes you have to alert me somethings
today is 20th
okay I have understand you
then we will be expecting you
Er r father
yess
I called you in peace this afternoon
my'niece is-Gpming at the end of tfiis month from abroad
Eeii then thank GOD, I will prepare somct’hing for her when she comes
father that is not what I meant
you know I didn't inform my niece when I was giving here to you
Eeeii really! !!
ï»¿
and you gave it to me7
and I gave it to you
did you thought about it
ofcourse I thought about it, but I gave it to you sake of how worried you were
I didn’t tell her
then why didn't you give me all of your money
father, is that what you are telling me7
oh what do you me to say7
look at how you and your wife were suffering, but beacuse of our friendship
I gave here to you for you to get a place to sleep look at what you telling me
so you mean charcoal sellers are not human beings what of those selling peper
can one cook his pantain without using charcoal?
or he will cook it in his mouth?
father look, I don’t want to argue with you
I said leave at the end of the month, my niece is coming from abroad
and I don't want her to come and meet you here so move out
eeiii I will never move out”
what do you mean by that9
ah young man
do you think I'm a shYall boy or what?7
father
I am staying here till death calls me
and you are here saying she is coming at the end of this month so I should move out
□ re you even normal7
young man it won't happen
I won't even leave if you rent me a house
you won't leave if I rent a room for you7
I swear on my fathers grave
do you think we the care takers are fools or what7
how can you move me out of here just like that?
is that fair?
whiles I have family
how can I get room within'g-a month'7
I won't even leave if you offer me 2 million
father??
is this my gratitude7
0<J
EenH
is this also my gratitude?
what are you doing?
what are you also doing7
don't I take care of here since I came7
If I were to be your Dad
would you allow me to sweep7
a marketer will lost every customer if she moves from here
what, have you been selling since you .came here
I sold braised rice with pepper
I have gain a lot of friend
how will I got access to them if I move from here
what do you want me to do for your friends
so becuasc of your friends I should give my house to you for free7
what I'm I doing with your friends
this smokers of yours
what I'm I doing with them
are smokers animals7'
are the smokers goats?
do animals smoke7
father
are foolish people the ones that smokes
so are coming to beat me?
are dogs the ones^that smaokes?
yielling
are you coming to beat me?
foolish man-
'm I a foolish man?
My foolishness is what gave your ass a place to sleeep
you were poor as hell as you were walking around
you were also poor as palm wine
I won't tell you anything, if you donit leave at end of this month I will myself
have you forget the military?
yoooo
errrmmmm
is true
I already alerted you guys before this meeting
sod
so you have discussed wifh each o'thef
Is now that we all have got time to do this meeting
so we don't have to waste time on this meeting
so this is the actual time has come forth
so today is today
I won't stretch this issue
v r
the main reason why I called you is
ï»¿
things have change this time around
so from now unwards
anyone who will give his money to Gospi concerning this house, is at your own risk
because if some arguements comes in terms of money issues
and I ask you for yours
and you tell me you have given it to Gospi
Errmm
I won't be able to face Gospi about it
you would have to pay again
that is why I am alerting you from today for you to be aware
so it won't be like as if you didn't hear
so if anyone have anything to say about what I just said, he can bring it out
okay, I don't understand somethings
so if I heard you right, the house is not for Gospi?
woman the house is not for her!
Eenii1!
Errm Bogi let me explain to her since she has asked
ï»¿
this house there
v»
is for my elder brother who lives in the states
for Gospi, I wouldn't say she is a stranger because we have known her for a while
Awe are familiar now so L know her
but she is not a family but a stranger \
eeii we are dead
so she came to beg for a-place t'o live
truthfully the house wasn't even roofed when she came in
so she came in as a care taker
till this time
so that is what it is
what is that supposed to mean?
I wouldn't want to go there Agya Fori, whatever the case is
you are even surprising'
Gospi had ti be here whiles you saying all this, or has she travel?
as for me I fought with her oo
I have told her that if she mistakenly cross me, I will deal with her
she is really disrespectful as shit
.so'as'tor me I have given her a warning, and you have to becareful with her too
you die when she enounters you with trouble and I don't want to die
from here I am going to my house
so you are at risk right now
so Borga's even know proverbs?
what can't you do if you are staying with Gospi, of what she is letting us go thru
if I unerstand you well
if the.house is not for Gpspi, why would you let her be in charge all this while?
Akwasi, Akwasi, I hatejwhat you are doing
didn't I pay rent, when I came in h'ece?
that-is the same money she uses to feed you
look at what you saying7
are you not dating her?
tenant who is dating a landlord
becareful if you are how coming to be n charge of here, he*like’s cheap things
ï»¿
why Eeii
you are enjoying in this house
mmmm
I will curse you if exchange contacts with her
crmm Borgi let me explain to him to clear-things out
ermmm brother
ease
as you asked
as you a'ske^d
' 4\ '-
the truth is 1
we didn't hear all these dealings when it started
it was too late by the time we heard and we have pardon her for that
we don't want it to happen again, that is why we are putting measures in place
so that nobody can claim some ownership along the line
that is why we are making you aware that from now unwards
events have turned
so like I said earlier on
we decided to let things slide
but now wc have noticed that if we don't take care things will go bad
so now, new king new law
ï»¿
so Gospi is not the landlord
and she has been disturbing us this way? we will deal with her
sandra be hurry and lets go
what's wrong
shouting'!'!!!'
sandra!!!1
ah Daddy, mummy
sandra just collapsed on our way going
Twum Barimah
Daddy
sandra!!1
what is wrong
sandra has collapsed
*"►*
eeiii sandra oh JESUS
SANDRA SANDRA "ii
CRYING"'
Gospi for you
say my name for me
you know what7?
I have been wanting to ask you this but, I always forget
a lady came here somedays ago
she called all of us and held a meeting with us all
but according to her this house is not for you
yes she said the house is for you but hyer brother's
and they gave here to you as a care taker or whatsoever
what7?
ï»¿
she said they gave it to you us a care taker
you forccfuly taken the house upon yourself and her brother has even forgotten about it
sol have always been wanting to ask you but, I forget all time
Akwasi so do you believe hat she is saying7
No I don't, that is why I am asking you
let me ask you, have you seen anybody claiming ownership of this house
Oh naa
haven't seen anything like that before
I struggled myself to build my house
why don't they wanna let me have my peace of mind
or is it a surprise or hatred
or the love I have got is what pains them, that I have to also get my lover?
maybe is the love you have got, is no big deal
what is it11!
I don't undersatnd somethings, what do they really want me to do in this house
forget it if it is not the truth
okay?
your anger is the reason I don't tell you anything
look at how your anger is coming up this short while
i'm not angry this is just a low a temper
I can see how it is rising now
sometimes you have to sit back and accept the case and know you next move
look if you know you will join them
let me know what I will do
I have even fed you with the advance you paid
do you have to say this all
you have been enjoying with club and all that
somebody might have heard all what you saying
Do I even care of anybody
Uncle
abena
this is my third day, I have been expecting you to take me to my house but still...
stay in your house?
yes my house
which house7?
what do you mean by that uncle?
the house I have been sending you money to build?
you came three days ago, and this is the place you have been staying
my wife will cook and feed you
so what do you mean by all that you saying?
Eee uncle
are you serious?
yess
uncle I'm talking about the house you have been sending me it's pictures
the one I sent money for you to build where you said you will take me when I come
Abena me?l 1!
what money have you sent to me?
Eem Abena
hey uncle becareful
I thought you were playing
the money I have been sending to you to build a house,
as you send me pictures all this while
oh my niece they have fraud you too
this is social media, they have fraud you
this is what these kids have been doing
then the pictures are photoshoped
how can the pictures you took youself be photoshoped
uncle don't make me do wild on you
Abena what are you talking about
you are telling me I sent the money to fraudsters7
hey Uncle
Abena
what are you doing?
do you know how I suffered abroad
do you know how much depression I went through
so you want to tell me you have spend the money
is there anybody home?
Uncle you want to tell me you have spend the money
which money?
heyyyy! >!
Uncle111
you have spent my money??
If you don't find me my house
is there not anybody home7
lUijl&J
Abena is everything okay"7
you are asking me this question?
becauses I'm surprise of what you saying7
Eeiii
you want me to struggle and bring you the money
to build house me
and you are asking me this bullshit7
Uncle uncle!!!!
how many times have I call you
Uncle be ready you arc taking me to the house okay
Uncle Uncle
has my nephew been smoking up there?
what money is she talking about
NO NO NO
if its not witches that are worrying her then she might be a smoker
ï»¿
herrr maame Yaa
why arc you taking so long in sweeping that small place?
Uncle I will finish very soon
when are you completing
Unclle we have to eat cassava oo
why so?
the yam is finished
be fast and come for money to go and buy some
you don't manage when there is yam, you have ti manage so we add stew with it
but you don't, now we have to go and buy some
look at how you are building
Oboy Aloo
'm the biggest
what do you mean by that, put the cutlass down and let me talk to you
I said put the cutlasss down and let me talk to you
Eeiii Anhwere
please I have puting it down
hernr ®6dy Aloo why?
what are we competing about
what is it<?
why look
let me tell you orfe thing
I'm notthe tyoe that you can bully and go scot free
I'm not the tyoe that you can bully and go scot free
oh that is really true
you have to also know that, force is used at whvere there is misunderstanding
thank you for saying that
look why!;??
why are you gossiping about me this way, what do you want7
about who?
about me!!
have I wrong you anyway7
on which way!!!7
why have I build my house and if people arc coming to rent you telrthem is not mine
stop that thing you have been doing or else things won't be fine betw.een the both of us
so this is why you were wondering me?
do you even look like a landlord7
why don't ® I p oU’^a s. s ii c h 7
and you have been telling them I used juju to snatchjfthe house and all that
people^use money to build but you use jCiju to build yours
you use juju for blocks, cements and even roofing sheets, I know all of that
,1 you don't stop that foolishness
look let me tell you one thing
tell me I'm listening
do you know how many times
I have been drugged me by juju
you7
kwame Anhwere company limited was my own company
ahhh!
you hear
then is easi to do juju
a human being pulled me down by juju you hear
as if today i’m doing same what is wrong .with it
go and asked pastors all over the country
Go and ask Duncan williams if I have sinned against’GOD
and I am saying things arc cheao now but becareful
don't point the cutlass .on me okay !!!
Uncle Uncle please have patient
Yaa Yaa this issue is not for the younger ones
even paliamentanans will fight over it
Herr Yaa talk to ypur uncle, children can also advice elderly ones
we maintain ones property but not destroying it
INSULTS!’!
uncle please calm down
talk to your uncle you can advice him as well
useless issue,
how can yoiu talk to me this way
come!1!!, why are you leaving7
oh Uncle sometimes you have to calm down (Yaa)
uncle so where is the huge money sister .even sent to me that I gave to you myself
and where is the house as well
ah Afia, why are you treating your own uncle as if I'm a kid
today this tomorrow that
see how Abena has been worrying me about money, what money have yoS given to me?
stop harrassing me this way
I want to have my peace
you are now asking us what money? Uncle?
I would have shut up if I don't know, but I have all my eyes in this
I sometimes bring some myself
sometimes the workers even comes to me for money
you said they were roofing the house, where is the house they were roofing?
ï»¿
Afia if you know where the house is then lets go show us so that allAvill be over
so i can have my peace
Have you heard him7
h'ave you heard what he is saying7
you are asking me the where about of the house7
this really going bad sister
he has blast
he is not his self
what, he is not his self
then wherever he is, he should bring his self here now and go search my house for me
or else I will pluck those your eyes from there
ï»¿
for what reason will you pluck my eyes
for dinner
what??’!
SHOUTING 111
ï»¿
Agya Twum
my niece
I come here with joy
you really glowing
ohhhh !!!
its all your help that is why I’m glowing
it's been a while
I'm around
how is your family
they are all tint?
thank GOD
let me find you some water to drink
oh no no is okay father
really7
yes
then what brings you here
I come in peace this evening
I used come to you sometime about where I was living, how my landlord was disturbing
and :y'ou fgave'Trie ^direction
and after I took that direction Agya Twum everthing is going smooth
they have even put my name after the area; AKUA GOSPI CONSTITUENCY
I am the queen over there
you are more than an MP
I tell you, I have rented some of the rooms and enjoying the money myself
that is all enjoy yourself
ahhhh!!
very'gpod
laughing...
ï»¿
is true that, peace of mind makes people forget about somethings
so now that you are coming to tell me, GOD bless you
oh not that father, I wanted to put some one or two things in place
I don't have anything bad in my mind
my directions always.comes through
I'm more than some pastors and prophets
father you are indeed a prophet, some prophets can't perform your what you did
a lot of them pass out revelations but it doesn't come true
but for me ot will come'through
'I told you the house will be yours
greet me you have done well
Agya Twum you are my savior
you are living somewhere and you want us to 'take care of your house#fpr you
are we the ones to keep there clean for you7
you are not serious to build a house
I will even snatch the throne from the president
eiii then you are serious
don't worry I'm still searching for somethings 20 cows and all that
I will snatch it at all from them
relax and andrstay in there for good
feel free ans sleep
I don't have anything against mankind
1 want the wellbeing of mankind
is time for we the care takers to enjoy lift?
yes we are tired
you can’t curse or kill us
ahh’h
.'ill sack you very soon
if I plant a gow arid face it at your end that is it for you you will never remember
you can even die and that will be all for you
brother can I see you for a moment7
Do you stay around7
yes please I stay around
'm looking for my house
some small house like that
small house??
yes
ah man are you okay?
I'm looking for my house, I can't find it
it's a small and fancy house it's very unique
ah are you saine?
how can a house got missing7
why are you insulting me
what you are asking me is very childish, ■even a land couldn't got missing
and do I look after peoples houses for them? there are a lot of them around check
I'm just asking about my missing house why this insult
madam this your man might be insane because even a land couldn't got missing
mine is kinda different that is why I'm asking you or are you new here
which of the houses here is not,looking nice, looks like your mind is crazy
brother is alright you can go
but what you said is really childish
uncle are you really okay?
Abena I'm really okay
Uncle are you really sure everything up here is okay?
Oh Abena I'm your uncle
then what is it
so uncle have you seen a missing house before?
that is what baffles me
have you hearde what he told you?
I am asking you
have you seen some before?
no you haven't? then why
thyen why do you want to disgrace me now
where is the room
abena calm down, you lets check around maybe I will find it
is there not where we came from
I'm asking you this; do you think I came from abraod just to tour here right?
ah!!!!
ï»¿
Uncle if you don't find my house for me we will wear the same shoe today
lets go, I will follow you everywhere
you go Im following you
be fast at your pace
sister you mean uncle took you around and couldn't firTd the house7
’ £ sister you mean uncle took you around and-coljTdn't'find the house?
nobody has ever walk with me this way all my life time
to. extent, of'asking someone he hasn't seen any short house in the house in the area
Eeiii really?
sister you know what don’t worry, will take you to a woman pastor ti help us in prayers
because this issue is very spiritual okay
be^a^e this isstie is ver*spiritual olcay^W
can she/really help us? (she is very good)
because'I.don’t.understand what is going EnT
she can really help us in prayers, because this is very bad
letsfgo my sister
| Amen'
(Amen)
Amen-1 ' (Amervy'
you are welcome
thank you
thank -you J
what'brings you here-tKis affer^noon
we come.in peace, this is my sister konadu, she stays in the OS
she sent money to my uncle for a house to live in when she comes
so when sbecame, she asked him-abbut the house
but he can't show us th^house, all he say is the house is miss7n§?
we don't even understand
A house can got missing
m.ummy-th'is.is very^irprising; J* I am aware of everthing that is'goin on
I didn't even know that a whole house can get missing
you may think this is some story but the truth, he cannot show us the house
it was very-irritating, so I decided to come to you because I'know what you can do
is only GOD that can help you and not me
t J^.just4a mer^SVmg, ■unless GOD intervene'orjelse I'm nothing
I'm just-a mere being, unless GOD intervene or else I'm nothing
we will all fast for thre^ays thaCis where GOD will reveaT things to us all
and then we all work on it together
Jzhe.sad-thihg is.y^loosing^ your property'to sorffeone else
the sad thing is you loosing your property to someone else
so after the fastingGOD will show us a way
.per what,he,has<shiown toj^ mea’ns^it’i’s’Yor ' " us and our children-b'utfflot for strangers
per what he has shown to us means it is for us and our children but not for strangers
GOD. will, make a'way
prophetess
surprisingly, my Uncle have been showing me kinds of pictures when I was there
but since I came, he can't even show me even one house telling me he canlt find it'
this-is-whatbaffles.m|B¥alot prophetess*
GOD is alive he will show us what to do he will help us get ours back
so calm down he’will talk for us
so calm down he will talk for us
is not our strengh nor yours that is why you can't arre"st him.
look Akonoba I really have
look Akonoba I really have a clean mind for everybody
can you please go straight to the point
so you want them to kill you before you know what is going on
something is really going on, you should know
can you please go straight to the point?
you ask your brother what is really going on between him and Gospi
sometimes I feel like they are dating, how tBt2y speak on phone
that is why she might be behaving like that
no no that is not true, my brother is not like that
she don't even like women like this
PROVERB
I think Gospi has bewithched your brother
Eeiiii
yesss
ahhhhhh 1111
you have said it
I'm telling you
what Lsaw sometime ago in the house was unc-alled for, I run away from the house
I m telling you
Eeiiii
you are very right1!
that is why I don't want to give my building to anybody to get a problem
no no I will never do that
borga is that how you are7
no no no what is hapening is very serious
betause what she has been doing these days is very 'serious
wfTen ’did your brother came from abroad?
No no
Akonoba, where wil we find a place to stay
I was staying in someones house but I was very clean and cool
you were even rewarding me that I\'m very calm and gentle
as for you I have in mind I will let you go stay and at my place
I don't understand the english you just said
I will let you stay in my new house I.am building sake of Akua Gospi
a lady like Akua Gospi can barnish you from abroad
Eeeii-borga
so won't you advice yourself about what is going on
you can't-trust anybody this time oo
Akonoba!1!!
is'that what you are telling me7
everybody is a suspect
ohh you too
oh live me too
Akonnoba find a church and go
im'JESUS name Amen
'.U ESU Sina me Amen
in JESUSiname Amen
welcome .myVda u g Pite r
thank you
•	*^	•	— v
what- hririgs^pu^hereBthis'afternoon
prophetess things are re’aliy\going bad
ï»¿
a young lady came and begged for a house to stay in fromrh'e.and my brother
holjsekofstaydih from me and my .brother *
a young lady came and begged for a house to stay in jfrom.me and my brother
I have never concord that\decission tilbhow
0&'°°
•' Ar but :Bco.ul3nit7sa J
; anythi rig* tc£m y ,B? o.t h er
but couldn't say anything to my>brot’her
, /but-I/cou13ntf?say anythincTto^my brother
I said everthing but my brother didn't mind me and went to prepare one for her
buftprophetess .
is getting serious.arid baffling
s-getting.serious and'baffling' '	- * - . ^^^.
is getting serious,and baffling
that girj went at our. back and rented the rooms to people
the one^-who' came to beg from you hbas given it for rent?
the one whotcame to beg from you hBas’ .giTeil ittfdrV^
no money hdyexpjanations to as and no permiss'icTn ifrom ianybody
no money no explarna^ons-to-as and no permission frdm\anybo'dy
she is now acting as a whole owner.of. the House
so I said I won't accept that
I told my pastor but/he was hesitating
eeii^w^i^^^
eeiiykwame! ••
he even,listens to what the lady sayskthan’ me
Ihe.even^listens^ro’what ^'ady^s ti^n.nFe
he even listens to what the lady says'than me
fie don't even pay?Keed vtd even us
the lady now is her family now
what-ma de me^ush^ditrerc js whatjjhe'' snakes 'f saw byer/there one aft’ern’oon
that is what brought me here
ï»¿
lady, the,figh't is.not your fight
this isVspiritually
..but I know'G'QD^will,fight(for us
' b u TL k' n o w '^Q D/ w 111 ';f i g h t f o r vu s'
GOD made ayitofeCs plan .nonsense sometime, so GOD will make any £lan;agaihst you vain
a'^'A ^ /'
so lets pray until y.our brother's mind wilfibeKat it’^state^firsf
so he can come here with^you too sp^GOD will talk-to you and giye. us-direction
s o • t h aV' h e c a n ?g e t: b a C k^h’ i sf p r op e ft y
• so pleasers not you fight, ^ f ;so don't try^to fTght.it yourself
so^p I ca se:i s-n ot^yp u ;f i
so don't tQ^^Jigh^itVourself
we are coming to<pray_
because we know.the problems already,-' today is when we have meet'to pray^
PRAYING !’M
ahh oh okay okay
then I'm waiting in front
AHHH hi
PRAYING! >«
JESUS CHRIST !«
HERRR ABENAA;
ABENAA
PRAYING
AMEN”
he has finished his^work ^hrough’the^ prayers, by tomorpwjGOD will bring victory
he has finished his work through the prayers, by tomorow GOD will bring victory
SINGlNGr^ND PRAYING
SINGING AND PRAYING
Father it will be wise for you.to stop what you are doing and worship GOD
Your mother migh't be daed right?
she died long ago but GOD is my mother
and you might not be married too
may GOD forgive you
may He forgive you
He should forgivge you too
are you from the north or Arabian
I'm the anointed on
who7 you?
I'm the one with the holy spirit
you are mad, you are a drunkard wo'ma
as he was talkin GOD is revealing somethings to me that
He has^illed his daughter for rituals for money
herr are you a foolish woman?
he\has <over'conquer the building
he has killed his daughter for rituals
Me is it me?
the one who Galled me 'is saying all that to me
are you going crazy
you can take me to where you want
I'm able in all things through chnst'^ho strenghtens me
is that what you telling me?-
what have you.seen7
is true you fight with the flesh but I fight with the name and the will of.GOD
PRAYING!!"
PW-INGP.u
will speak
I have sin
I will speak-
what will youpay
1& ^i&PJ^ Hy y)]^ r .	. - - ।
worrying me not being a responsible
39 J 'Wan'S cj juju nian .fo? Juju
nana please Km serious
nana I ca e here to tell you
he has even.come again to.sack^me away
s i ^rKv
nana I have nobody to turn to but-you, so I beg you dSn’t turn me/down
' for whato’-
for what?
help me Nana
I '.vi 11 help you
do you want the house to be yours forever.
ofcourse Nana, who doesn't wanna go to heaven
but there is trouble
nana what is it tell me I will do it
1 will need blood
which kind of blood7
human blood
ahh Nana is too much
J1 '/Jiu. zjkiD ji£ >u x>^ y^p
Eeiii Nana
you suffer to get the best thing done
and don't talk trush as well
;JrrJ JWx £jJk ifrif^ ;£> ”
herrr Twum Banmah
s that how you are 77
Twum1
you were sleepin outside and I helped you find a place to stay and even buy you food
so my niece has been fighting with me all this while is your fault
stop that foolishness1 master
I wanted to snatch the house from him
Twum barimah is that what you have done to me7
so you killed my daughter
FIGHTING'!
lets give it to GOD, he will judge him not you
ahhhhhhh MH
MAD!!!
This is what happens to the one wjo doesn't seek GOD in all his doings
ï»¿
as I was saying the shops are two
one deals with spare parts so I want you to join them as a shop keeper
at the end of the day you will get something for yourself and your niece
than to stay at home without doing anything
first of all thank you very much
/ A\ A \-r ? -
you are very supportive and the one who help his fellow helps himself
you have surprised me
PROVERB...
why will I reject working to help my own self I’m I a fool7
I grab it madam
and I thank you very much for thinking about me
and what you are doing to me, I don't know when I can repay
I thank you
GOD. only deserves to be thanked
and secondly, I know its hard to say but I have to say it
you know how I be paying rent all this while at my current place to landlord
and I really pay a huge amount of money
so since my rent ended I have been thinking about what I'm going to do
It's very worrisome
and with your help the house is now a better place now
So I want to come and stay here
I donit wanna pay any money to any landlord again but complete this and move in
so if I should build a two bed room for you back there with your niece
or I should rent some place for you
tell me whatever you want so I could know what to do
madam I thank you again for the first time
don't thank me man.
I knew what you wanted to say when you started talking
because I have heard it many times
it doen’t make any sense for you to rent a house whiles you have this here
everybody has come to live in their own in this area
so I thank idea is not bad
but I can't force you to build me a boys quarters or rent me a room
will do whatever you tell me to do sake of what you have done for me
you are giving me a job and at the same time thinking about where I will sleep
you are not even in but you arc thinking about me and where I will sleep
It means you think and care about human
some landlords won't let you even come back from work but will move you out
how some Gare takers also use various means to dupe the house later he is been sacked
if every lanlord have such kindness in this’ world, the world would be a better place
we have to all gam something from each other but not one sided
don't let-this kindness end here but extend it to the everywhere you go
>& n
there is blessings in giving that receiving
and GOD will always replace your loses
so everything you are willing to do for us, we will manage
oh okay because, If I try to let them build it might take some time
so I will rent a place for you
that wil also let me work hard because I know I have a rent to pay
Yaa speaks english with me when she comes back from school and that is because of you
hmmm Akwes
you know you are my paddy
the gossip you gossip about Ofori to Gospi is too much becareful
ah Borga what do you mean
you are exception to all her shoutings so you go scot free
she shout at yo'u if you .don't arrange your things^well
No this, is gossiping > •
what gossiping77
oh put your things in good shape does ofon pays any rent7
oh put your thmgs|ifTgood shape does ofori pays-any rent?
who are these people
they ^re all tenants
Gospi gave them this place right7
yes.
herrrTGall her for me where is that Gospi
where is she
come on come out!!
you are yawning
you thought you could go scot free
look at the way she has opened her mouth like a crocodile
Gome onTcome out here
why didn't you even alert me before coming
is that how you are Gospi
Bra KwarrTe is something wrong?
>§fth'(grhdpmg yooi?
I told you that it will all come to an end
this is the end for you
darkness couldn't'overcome the light, so be ready
exchanging words
is this how you repaying me ??
remember when you came to me to beg for a place to sleep
remember
ï»¿
Do well and finish some of them and stop buying a lot of land
its bit^y’bif
its bit by bit
please Good afternoon
ï»¿
can I have a little conversadon^with' you?« j
ofcourse yes what is it?
please is this house you house
yes its mine, the area boys comes here right?
I don't even know any area boy
I came beg for something please
what is it please
o
O
g Hi# ‘ B©Ci © T/W
BEGGING FOR A PLACE TO STAY
BEGGING FOR A PLACE O STAY
Eeiii Gospi is that how you are7
she is a woman satan thaUybu are living witfi God knows what she has'done to do you
all that^silly th'in’gs you did, sake of the will of G@D everything over now
Bra kwame it's the devi
ernn what satan
I beg you in the name of GOD
Bra Kwame please forgive me
please I beg you
I should forgive you7
it means I have wasted my energy and money all this ,wKile sake.-of you juju
bra Kwame its the devil
and you ahve make look like a foolish guy walking around
I don't even listen to my won my own sister
you have make somebody's son like a fool
don't talk much, get in there and pick you bag and leave my house
‘I don't need you here anymore
I wifli shp you if you touch me
MOVING HER OUT
ï»¿
Let him follow her, she stays with her too
what have I done7
didn't Vou see what' nonsense he was asking
then come and go
Borga I don't know you
you have paid what??
herrr what nonsense
MOVING HIM OUT"!
how could you do this, didn't expect that from you
you took mum to juju and turn her mind away from the house why are you that wicked
don't beg me move out or else my mum will come and shoot you
ï»¿
HIEFH’iiH!